<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:contextHubPath="/etc/cloudsettings/default/contexthub"
        cq:contextHubSegmentsPath="/etc/segmentation/contexthub"
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2017-11-27T18:19:13.334+01:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="fr20437"
        cq:lastReplicated="{Date}2017-11-27T18:28:22.476+01:00"
        cq:lastReplicatedBy="fr20437"
        cq:lastReplicationAction="Activate"
        cq:tags="[article:general]"
        cq:template="/apps/gotomarket/templates/releasearticle"
        jcr:description="London, 19 August 2014 - The introduction of a state-of-the-art ticketing and online booking system by award-winning ferry operator Caledonian MacBrayne (CalMac) has taken a step closer with the award of a contract to Worldline, the European leader and a global player in the payments and transactional services industry."
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-08-29T17:27:52.108+02:00"
        jcr:lastModifiedBy="a101309"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Award-winning ferry operator on track for new ticketing system"
        jcr:uuid="8d80f227-0fe6-4cb7-9381-c71ef9a74a87"
        sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/pages/releasearticle"
        brand="worldline"
        categories_x0040_TypeHint="String[]"
        creationDate="{Date}2014-08-19T10:00:00.000+02:00"
        hideInNav="false"
        imagePath="/content/dam/gotomarket/uploads/bg-header-industries.jpg"
        keywords="worldline, award, ferry, ticketing"
        showbrand="false"
        showinfostrip="false">
        <head
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/head"/>
        <headlibs
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/headlibs"/>
        <header
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/header">
            <leftnavigation
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/leftnavigation"
                iconClass="iconClass2"/>
            <rightnavigation
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/rightnavigation"
                iconClass="iconClass2">
                <countrylistdropdown
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/countrylistdropdown"/>
                <languagedropdown
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/languagedropdown"/>
            </rightnavigation>
            <mainnav
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/mainnav"/>
            <infostrip
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/infostrip"/>
            <breadcrumb
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/breadcrumb"/>
        </header>
        <headerpage
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/headerpage"/>
        <releasetitle
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/releasetitle"/>
        <key
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/parsys">
            <releasekeymessages
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/releasekeymessages"/>
        </key>
        <releasedescription
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/releasedescription"/>
        <prshare
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/prshare"/>
        <footer
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/footer">
            <sitemap
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/sitemap"/>
            <followus
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/followus"/>
            <newsletterform
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/newsletterform"/>
        </footer>
        <footlibs
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/footlibs"/>
        <copyright
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/copyright"/>
        <content
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/parsys">
            <grid
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-08-29T17:23:43.178+02:00"
                jcr:createdBy="a101309"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-08-29T17:23:43.178+02:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="a101309"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/layout/grid">
                <column1 jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured">
                    <richtext
                        jcr:created="{Date}2017-08-29T17:23:59.181+02:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="a101309"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-08-29T17:27:16.302+02:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="a101309"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/content/richtext"
                        text="&lt;p>&lt;b>London, 19 August 2014 - The introduction of a state-of-the-art ticketing and online booking system by award-winning ferry operator Caledonian MacBrayne (CalMac) has taken a step closer with the award of a contract to Worldline, the European leader and a global player in the payments and transactional services industry.&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>The initial three-year contract will see Worldline, a specialist in online transactions, team up with Hogia, the largest provider of IT systems for ferry and sea freight operators for the European transport market, to deliver a modern, integrated ticketing system to support lifeline ferry services on the west coast of Scotland.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Martin Dorchester, Managing Director of CalMac, said: “We have received a raft of awards in recent years in recognition of our focus on customer care but we know we can always do more to improve the customer experience and that is why we are currently undertaking a major programme of improvements to modernise our systems to help us be the best we can be. The award of this contract is an important milestone in that journey as we recognise that our ticketing and online booking systems are starting to show their age and no longer meet the expectations of customers for whom e-ticketing and the use of mobile technology is becoming the norm.”&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>“The two companies selected to work with us have unrivalled experience in this field providing between them similar services for a host of rail and ferry operators both in the UK and overseas and we are sure all of our customers will find the new systems easy to use and greatly enhance their experience of travelling with us.”&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Scottish Government Transport Minister, Keith Brown MSP, said: “The award of this contract is excellent news, as it brings CalMac another step closer to delivering a state-of-the-art ticketing and booking system that will provide real benefits to ferry passengers. The system will make it quicker and easier for travellers to make bookings and reservations, and will allow smart ticketing technology to be rolled out in the future. I want ferry travel in Scotland to remain an attractive option, and this new system will help enhance the customer experience on board CalMac services.”&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>The contract is being award by CalMac’s parent company David MacBrayne Ltd. in order that the technology is available for services provided by CalMac Ferries Ltd and Argyll Ferries Ltd services and other ferry services it may operate in the future.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Worldline [Euronext:WLN], an Atos company and the European leader and a global player in the payments and transactional services industry, currently provides similar services to rail companies across Scotland, England and Europe as well as operating ticket website redspottedhanky.com.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Hogia provides ferry reservation and ticketing systems to ferry companies across the world including, Red Funnel in the UK, Destination Gotland in Sweden and Wagenborg Passenger Services in the Netherlands.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Atos Senior Vice President in Scotland, Gavin Thomson, said the company was delighted to have been awarded the opportunity to support one of Scotland’s iconic businesses: “With the skills and breadth of experience we have across the company, we are ready to support David MacBrayne’s current and future ambitions through this contract,” he said.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Lisa Coleman, CEO at Worldline in the UK &amp;amp; Ireland, said, “Working with our partner Hogia, we have extensive experience in providing ticketing and reservations as well as back office services which support transport companies across the world. We are committed to both David MacBrayne and CalMac’s vision and passion for supporting rural communities, tourism industry and their own business transformation.”&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Atos has invested heavily in people in Scotland and our highly experienced and motivated team of more than 1500 business technologists work in locations across Scotland including Livingston, Glasgow, Dundee, Edinburgh and Forres.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h3>About Worldline&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>Worldline [Euronext:WLN] is the European leader and a global player in the payments and transactional services industry. Worldline delivers new-generation services, enabling its customers to offer smooth and innovative solutions to the end consumer. Key actor for B2B2C industries, with 40 years of experience, Worldline supports and contributes to the success of all businesses and administrative services in a perpetually evolving market. Worldline offers a unique and flexible business model built around a global and growing portfolio, thus enabling end-to-end support. Worldline activities are organised around three axes: Merchant Services &amp;amp; Terminals, Mobility &amp;amp; e-Transactional Services, Financial Processing Services &amp;amp; Software Licensing. Worldline employs more than 7,200 people worldwide and generated 1.12 billion euros revenues (pro forma) in 2013. Worldline is an Atos company. &lt;a title=&quot;www.worldline.com&quot; href=&quot;http://www.worldline.com&quot;>www.worldline.com&lt;b>&lt;/b>&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h3>For more information, please contact:&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Tessa David&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xa;+44 20 7830 1977&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;a title=&quot;Tessa.david@atos.net&quot; href=&quot;mailto:Tessa.david@atos.net&quot;>Tessa.david@atos.net&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                        textIsRich="true"/>
                </column1>
            </grid>
        </content>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
