<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:contextHubPath="/etc/cloudsettings/default/contexthub"
        cq:contextHubSegmentsPath="/etc/segmentation/contexthub"
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2017-10-09T14:48:41.471+02:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="a598986"
        cq:lastReplicated="{Date}2017-10-30T17:57:28.202+01:00"
        cq:lastReplicatedBy="a631192"
        cq:lastReplicationAction="Activate"
        cq:tags="[blog:mobility,blog:corporate]"
        cq:template="/apps/gotomarket/templates/blogarticle"
        jcr:description="Internal mobility, a key part of our HR strategy, is a career’s development tool, which grants more flexibility to teams, enabling them to remain in motion for the well-being of team members and companies alike. Laurence Poilfoulot and Laurette Vandenplas discuss internal mobility and present Worldline’s HR initiatives on this matter."
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-09-11T10:56:33.280+02:00"
        jcr:lastModifiedBy="a646217"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Worldline expands its people's professional horizons"
        jcr:uuid="f3ba00e4-8fd2-41cd-b879-4e57f01dd3be"
        sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/pages/blogarticle"
        authorImage="/content/dam/worldline/images/blog/author/wl.png"
        authorName="Laurence Poilfoullot and Laurette Vandenplas"
        authorText="Human Resources"
        categories="[category:talents]"
        categories_x0040_TypeHint="String[]"
        creationDate="{Date}2016-11-25T10:00:00.000+01:00"
        hideInNav="false"
        imagePath="/content/dam/worldline/images/blog/header/bg-blue-bubble.jpg"
        isExternalContactUsUrl="false"
        isExternalJoinUsUrl="false"
        isStickyContactHidden="false"
        noExtentionContactUs="false"
        noExtentionJoinUs="false"
        showbrand="false"
        showinfostrip="false"
        title="Worldline expands its people's professional horizons ">
        <head
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/head"/>
        <headlibs
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/headlibs"/>
        <header
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/header">
            <leftnavigation
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/leftnavigation"
                iconClass="iconClass2"/>
            <rightnavigation
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/rightnavigation"
                iconClass="iconClass2">
                <countrylistdropdown
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/countrylistdropdown"/>
                <languagedropdown
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/languagedropdown"/>
            </rightnavigation>
            <mainnav
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/mainnav"/>
            <infostrip
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/infostrip"/>
            <breadcrumbblog
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/breadcrumbblog"/>
        </header>
        <headerblog
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/headerblog"/>
        <singleauthor
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/singleauthor"/>
        <prshare
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/prshare"/>
        <stayintouch
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/stayintouch"/>
        <footer
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/footer">
            <sitemap
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/sitemap"/>
            <followus
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/followus"/>
            <newsletterform
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/newsletterform"/>
        </footer>
        <footlibs
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/footlibs"/>
        <copyright
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/copyright"/>
        <content
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/parsys">
            <richtext
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-09-07T11:29:34.047+02:00"
                jcr:createdBy="a101309"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-09-07T11:31:22.274+02:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="a101309"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/content/richtext"
                text="&lt;p>&lt;i>&lt;b>Laurence Poilfoulot&lt;/b> is Global Head of Recruitment and Mobility for Worldline. She joined us in 2001.&lt;/i>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;i>&lt;b>Laurette Vandenplas &lt;/b>is HR Director for Worldline Benelux and HR Business Partner for Merchant Services and Terminals. She joined the company in 1992.&lt;/i>&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                textIsRich="true"/>
            <richtext_690559434
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-09-07T11:31:32.827+02:00"
                jcr:createdBy="a101309"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-09-07T11:32:54.744+02:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="a101309"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/content/richtext"
                text="&lt;h2>Can you briefly define the concept of internal mobility?&lt;/h2>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Laurence&lt;/b>: Internal mobility consists in changing position while staying in the same company. For example, the collaborator can change position, or work on another market, be promoted to a higher position, or change offices and even relocate to another country.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Laurette&lt;/b>: A key element to remember about internal mobility is that it offers as many possibilities as there are different profiles in a company. Each team member is unique and builds his/her own career according to his/her skills and his/her state of mind.&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                textIsRich="true"/>
            <richtext_532367123
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-09-07T11:33:07.924+02:00"
                jcr:createdBy="a101309"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-09-07T11:33:51.926+02:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="a101309"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/content/richtext"
                text="&lt;h2>In the current economic context, why should we encourage internal mobility?&lt;/h2>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Laurence&lt;/b>: Internal mobility is a career’s development tool, and encouraging internal mobility grants more flexibility to teams, enabling them to remain in motion for the well-being of our people and of our company.&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                textIsRich="true"/>
            <richtext_341130289
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-09-07T11:33:59.619+02:00"
                jcr:createdBy="a101309"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-09-07T11:34:44.483+02:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="a101309"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/content/richtext"
                text="&lt;h2>What are the advantages of internal mobility for the company and for our people?&lt;/h2>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Laurette&lt;/b>: Several advantages are directly linked to internal mobility. On one hand, it enables the company to motivate and satisfy its people with new opportunities. Moreover, it allows us to highlight the knowledge and the experience of our people in different contexts and sectors. On the other hand, internal mobility leads to polyvalent team members who are more aware of every aspect of the company. Thus, internal mobility is both a source of motivation for our people who can use it to limitlessly make their career evolve and it also provides the company with varied profiles.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Laurence&lt;/b>: Internal mobility can also be considered as a training tool because it allows team members to develop their skills and to stimulate their capability to adapt, which is a popular quality for companies, by changing perimeter or team. In addition, it retains the talents we hire, more specifically younger talents, who constantly crave change.&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                textIsRich="true"/>
            <richtext_1532826672
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-09-07T11:36:06.105+02:00"
                jcr:createdBy="a101309"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-09-07T11:36:36.830+02:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="a101309"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/content/richtext"
                text="&lt;h2>Within the company, what are the conditions and tools that encourage internal mobility?&lt;/h2>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Laurence&lt;/b>: In order to make internal mobility possible, the company has to be international, which is the case with Worldline, which is present in 20 different countries. Managers also play a key role in the success of the company’s mobility strategy. Indeed, it is essential for them to support this mobility, a key point we encourage inside our company. Another important prerequisite to internal mobility is transparency based on communication. This means that everyone should have access to all opportunities. The Job Café launched in Belgium is a good example of this transparency, since team members benefit from in-person discussions about different opportunities, jobs and projects.&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                textIsRich="true"/>
            <richtext_1411235835
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-09-07T11:36:54.759+02:00"
                jcr:createdBy="a101309"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-09-07T11:38:24.701+02:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="a101309"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/content/richtext"
                text="&lt;h2>Laurette, can you tell us more about the Job Café initiative of Worldline Belgium?&lt;/h2>&#xa;&lt;p>The aim of the Job Café is to stimulate internal mobility, but also to make sure that it is accepted and fully integrated within our corporate culture.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Concretely, the Job Café enables any team member to meet Hiring Managers in a convivial place. The strength of the Job Café initiative is that it takes place in a casual atmosphere, facilitating the involvement of team members. Thus, team members and Hiring Managers can easily exchange and discuss about internal opportunities. Today, the first Belgian Job Cafés have already led to several internal transfers.&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                textIsRich="true"/>
            <richtext_363795076
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-09-07T11:38:52.384+02:00"
                jcr:createdBy="a101309"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-09-07T11:39:41.286+02:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="a101309"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/content/richtext"
                text="&lt;h2>In your opinion, will the use of internal mobility increase in the next few years and why?&lt;/h2>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Laurette&lt;/b>: I think so. We can already see it in Belgium, with already 40 persons having internally transferred in the first semester only. This evolution is a direct result of all the communication efforts and the transparency that Worldline has set up, which has enabled our people to have access to information easily and to be supported during their thought process and in their choice.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Laurence&lt;/b>: Moreover, the recent creation of the “Head of Mobility” position demonstrates Worldline’s will to develop internal mobility and to frame in a way that enables our people to evolve in the best possible conditions, by continuing, for instance, to promote initiatives, such as Job Cafés, throughout our locations. We have already received a lot of positive feedback on this initiative, from both team members and managers.&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                textIsRich="true"/>
            <richtext_1012024163
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-09-07T11:39:56.683+02:00"
                jcr:createdBy="a101309"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-09-07T11:41:00.303+02:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="a101309"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/content/richtext"
                text="&lt;h2>Thank you for your time today, Laurence and Sarah. I will leave you with one final question: in your opinion, what will be the invention/innovation that will change our world in a century?&lt;/h2>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Laurence&lt;/b>: In my opinion, we will probably use images/videos for everything in a century, that is to say that we will no longer write, we will only communicate by videos. I can already see it in recruiting where we receive more and more video CVs for instance.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Laurette&lt;/b>: In a century, I hope that we will have discovered other living species, other inhabited planets. And that we will also be able to communicate with these new species.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Laurence&lt;/b>: We’ll then do galactic mobility [laughs].&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                textIsRich="true"/>
        </content>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
