<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:contextHubPath="/etc/cloudsettings/default/contexthub"
        cq:contextHubSegmentsPath="/etc/segmentation/contexthub"
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2017-11-27T18:13:04.796+01:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="fr20437"
        cq:lastReplicated="{Date}2017-11-27T18:13:16.742+01:00"
        cq:lastReplicatedBy="fr20437"
        cq:lastReplicationAction="Activate"
        cq:tags="[article:]"
        cq:template="/apps/gotomarket/templates/releasearticle"
        jcr:description="Bezons, 26 January 2016 - Worldline (Euronext: WLN], European market leader in payments and transactional services, provides a new electronic signature service complying with the new EU electronic trust services regulation (elDAS - electronic Identification and Authentication Services), based on technologies developed by Bull, the Atos brand for technology products and software."
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-11-27T18:13:04.792+01:00"
        jcr:lastModifiedBy="fr20437"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Worldline announced a new digital signature solution integrating Bull cybersecurity technologies"
        jcr:uuid="636a195a-a85a-4bcb-91d6-0bf1d2bae7bb"
        sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/pages/releasearticle"
        brand="worldline"
        categories="[article:]"
        categories_x0040_TypeHint="String[]"
        creationDate="{Date}2016-01-26T18:12:00.000+01:00"
        hideInNav="false"
        imagePath="/content/dam/gotomarket/uploads/bg-header-industries.jpg"
        isExternalContactUsUrl="false"
        isExternalJoinUsUrl="false"
        isStickyContactHidden="false"
        keywords="Worldline announced, digital signature solution, Bull cybersecurity technologies&#xd;&#xa;"
        noExtentionContactUs="false"
        noExtentionJoinUs="false"
        showbrand="false"
        showinfostrip="false">
        <head
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/head"/>
        <headlibs
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/headlibs"/>
        <header
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/header">
            <leftnavigation
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/leftnavigation"
                iconClass="iconClass2"/>
            <rightnavigation
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/rightnavigation"
                iconClass="iconClass2">
                <countrylistdropdown
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/countrylistdropdown"/>
                <languagedropdown
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/languagedropdown"/>
            </rightnavigation>
            <mainnav
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/mainnav"/>
            <infostrip
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/infostrip"/>
            <breadcrumb
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/breadcrumb"/>
        </header>
        <headerpage
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/headerpage"/>
        <releasetitle
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/releasetitle"/>
        <key
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/parsys">
            <releasekeymessages
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/releasekeymessages"/>
        </key>
        <releasedescription
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/releasedescription"/>
        <prshare
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/prshare"/>
        <footer
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/footer">
            <sitemap
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/sitemap"/>
            <followus
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/followus"/>
            <newsletterform
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/newsletterform"/>
        </footer>
        <footlibs
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/footlibs"/>
        <copyright
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/copyright"/>
        <content
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/parsys">
            <grid
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-08-28T10:46:11.933+02:00"
                jcr:createdBy="a646217"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-08-28T10:46:11.933+02:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="a646217"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/layout/grid">
                <column1
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/parsys">
                    <richtext
                        jcr:created="{Date}2017-08-28T10:46:19.765+02:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="a646217"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-08-28T10:53:18.815+02:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="a646217"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/content/richtext"
                        text="&lt;p>&lt;b>Bezons, 26 January 2016 - Worldline (Euronext: WLN], European market leader in payments and transactional services, provides a new electronic signature service complying with the new EU electronic trust services regulation (elDAS - electronic Identification and Authentication Services), based on technologies developed by Bull, the Atos brand for technology products and software.&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>The planned service provides for issue of an electronic signature that is as binding as a handwritten signature. Pursuant to the new regulation, several methods are offered for qualified signatures of legal and natural persons:&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;ul>&#xa;&lt;li>Under the local method, a smart card is used to produce the signature as close as possible to consumers.&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>Under the central method, the need for a smart card can be avoided while satisfying regulatory security requirements.&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;/ul>&#xa;&lt;p>These solutions are open and can be combined with other Worldline offers such as signature circuits, timestamps and secure document archiving in order to provide end-to-end customer service. These innovations, developed by two trusted companies, represent a new source of growth with a view to supporting European companies in their digital transformations, by providing electronic documents guaranteeing authenticity and correct identity.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Chris Moret, Vice-President Cybersecurity at Atos, said: &lt;i>&amp;quot;At a time when the EU seeks to grow electronic cross-border transactions with the eIDAS regulation, Worldline's business expertise and capacity to deal with huge volumes of secure electronic transactions, and Bull's high-tech excellence in cybersecurity, combine to mark a large step forward in European digital trust&amp;quot;. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/i>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Olivier Stuckens, Worldline Managing Director Mobility and e-transactional services, commented:&lt;i> &amp;quot;With this new qualified signature offer, Worldline is sharing its vision and innovation with European companies. As such, we are helping customers to take full advantage of the digital revolution thanks to these new regulatory advances by providing all levels of authorized electronic signatures and related services.&amp;quot;&lt;/i>&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;br>&#xa;Worldline will showcase this new solution at the 8th Cybersecurity International Forum in Lille, on 25th and 26th February 2016, on the Atos booth B5.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h3>Expertise in cybersecurity&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>Atos has over 4500 security professionals worldwide, who manage 100 million identities every day; monitor 2 million events every hour in one of the Atos Security Operational Centers and through Worldline secure 5 billion transactions each year. The Atos security portfolio covers the complete range of services from mobile security, fraud management through to secure innovation platforms and trusted cloud services. Additionally, Atos recently unveiled its Cybersecurity vision in a dedicated campaign: &amp;quot;Ready for Anything”.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h3>About Bull&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>Bull is an Atos brand for high-tech products and software sold in over 50 countries around the world. Backed by a history of over 80 years of high-tech innovations, 2,000 patents and over 700 R&amp;amp;D experts supported by the Atos scientific community, Bull provides Atos Group customers with value-enhancing products and software with a view to supporting them in their digital transformation to meet big data and cyberthreat challenges.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>As European market leader in High Performance Computing (HPC), Bull has developed numerous reputable solutions including 'Bullx' - a low power consumption supercomputer based on a Bull patented system, 'Bullion' - one of the most powerful x86 servers in the world to satisfy big data requirements, 'Evidian' - security software providing Identity and Access Management (IAM), 'TrustWay' - secure HSM cryptographic modules, and 'Hoox' - an ultra secure smartphone.&lt;br>&#xa;Learn more at: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bull.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>www.bull.com&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h3>About Worldline&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>Worldline (Euronext: WLN) is European market leader in payments and transactional services. Worldline delivers new-generation services, enabling customers to offer smooth and innovative solutions to the end consumer. As a key B2B2C supplier with over 40 years experience, Worldline supports and contributes to the success of all private and public sector entities in a perpetually evolving market. Worldline offers a unique and flexible business model built around a global and growing portfolio, thus enabling end-to-end support. Worldline operates based on three divisions: Merchant Services &amp;amp; Terminals, Mobility &amp;amp; e-Transactional Services, Financial Processing &amp;amp; Software Licensing. Worldline employs more than 7,300 people worldwide and posted 2014 revenues of €1.15 billion. Worldline is an Atos company. &lt;a href=&quot;http://worldline.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>worldline.com&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h3>Worldline Press Contact:&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Cendrella Bourjaili&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xa;Email: &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:cendrella.bourjaili@worldline.com&quot;>cendrella.bourjaili@worldline.com&lt;/a>&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                        textIsRich="true"/>
                </column1>
            </grid>
        </content>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
