<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:contextHubPath="/etc/cloudsettings/default/contexthub"
        cq:contextHubSegmentsPath="/etc/segmentation/contexthub"
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2017-11-27T17:09:00.234+01:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="fr20437"
        cq:lastReplicated="{Date}2017-11-29T17:32:49.014+01:00"
        cq:lastReplicatedBy="fr20437"
        cq:lastReplicationAction="Activate"
        cq:template="/apps/gotomarket/templates/releasearticle"
        jcr:description="Bezons, October 24th, 2017 – Worldline, [Euronext: WLN] European leader in the payments and transactional services industry, has committed to contribute to the Sustainable Development Goals (SDGs), a universal, global and inclusive action and roadmap launched by the United Nations (UN) to end poverty, protect the planet and ensure prosperity and peace for all by 2030, after releasing its first UN Global Compact Communication on Progress,. Through its sustainable solutions and its value chain, Worldline is involved in achieving the 17 SDGs, however the company has decided to concentrate its efforts on the 5 most relevant SDGs for its organization and its business activities.&#xd;&#xa;"
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-11-27T17:09:00.229+01:00"
        jcr:lastModifiedBy="fr20437"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Worldline is committed to support the United Nations’ Sustainable Development Goals"
        jcr:uuid="248d71a5-889d-4bcc-ba79-7de6e13db9b7"
        sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/pages/releasearticle"
        creationDate="{Date}2017-10-24T18:15:00.000+02:00"
        hideInNav="false"
        imagePath="/content/dam/gotomarket/uploads/bg-header-industries.jpg"
        isExternalContactUsUrl="false"
        isExternalJoinUsUrl="false"
        isStickyContactHidden="false"
        noExtentionContactUs="false"
        noExtentionJoinUs="false"
        showbrand="false"
        showinfostrip="false">
        <head
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/head"/>
        <headlibs
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/headlibs"/>
        <header
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/header">
            <leftnavigation
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/leftnavigation"
                iconClass="iconClass2"/>
            <rightnavigation
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/rightnavigation"
                iconClass="iconClass2">
                <countrylistdropdown
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/countrylistdropdown"/>
                <languagedropdown
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/languagedropdown"/>
            </rightnavigation>
            <mainnav
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/mainnav"/>
            <infostrip
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/infostrip"/>
            <breadcrumb
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/breadcrumb"/>
        </header>
        <headerpage
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/headerpage"/>
        <releasetitle
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/releasetitle"/>
        <key
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/parsys">
            <releasekeymessages
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/releasekeymessages"/>
        </key>
        <releasedescription
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/releasedescription"/>
        <prshare
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/prshare"/>
        <footer
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/footer">
            <sitemap
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/sitemap"/>
            <followus
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/followus"/>
            <newsletterform
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/newsletterform"/>
        </footer>
        <footlibs
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/footlibs"/>
        <copyright
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/copyright"/>
        <content
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/parsys">
            <grid
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-10-24T18:02:29.249+02:00"
                jcr:createdBy="fr20437"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-10-24T18:02:29.249+02:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="fr20437"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/layout/grid">
                <column1
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/parsys">
                    <richtext
                        jcr:created="{Date}2017-10-24T18:02:41.469+02:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="fr20437"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-10-24T18:16:08.393+02:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="fr20437"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/content/richtext"
                        text="&lt;p>&lt;b>Bezons, October 24th, 2017 – Worldline, [Euronext: WLN] European leader in the payments and transactional services industry, has committed to contribute to the Sustainable Development Goals (SDGs), a universal, global and inclusive action and roadmap launched by the United Nations (UN) to end poverty, protect the planet and ensure prosperity and peace for all by 2030, after releasing its first UN Global Compact Communication on Progress,. Through its sustainable solutions and its value chain, Worldline is involved in achieving the 17 SDGs, however the company has decided to concentrate its efforts on the 5 most relevant SDGs for its organization and its business activities.&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;b>&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Based on the most material CSR topics for its stakeholders and for its business activities, Worldline has identified 5 primary SDGs on which the company has the most significant impact and can maximize its contribution:&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;ul>&#xa;&lt;li>&lt;span class=&quot;styled&quot;>To promote peace, justice and strong institutions (SDG 16),&lt;/span>&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>&lt;span class=&quot;styled&quot;>To ensure a decent work and economic growth (SDG 8),&lt;/span>&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>&lt;span class=&quot;styled&quot;>To be involved in climate action (SDG 13),&lt;/span>&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>&lt;span class=&quot;styled&quot;>To ensure responsible production and consumption (SDG 12),&lt;/span>&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>&lt;span class=&quot;styled&quot;>To ensure inclusive and equitable quality education (SDG 4).&lt;/span>&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;/ul>&#xa;&lt;p>In addition, Worldline also has a particular impact on 2 complementary SDGs, SDG 3 “Good health and well-being” and SDG 5 “Gender Equality” covering two areas in which the company is highly involved through its wellbeing@worldline and Gender Equity programs.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Reinforcing value for clients through sustainable and innovative solutions represents a key challenge in Worldline’s CSR strategy. As a result, Worldline designs and offers sustainable solutions that provide its clients with economic, social and environmental benefits that mainly contribute to the SDG 8 “Decent work and economic growth”, SDG 9 “Industry, innovation and infrastructure”, SDG 10 “Reduced inequalities”, SDG 13 “Climate action” and SDG 16 “Peace, justice and strong institutions”. For instance, Worldline’s Fraud Risk Management, E-banking or Acquiring Processing solutions enable the decrease of fraud and corruption risks and the prevention of cyber threats, thus contributing to the achievement of the SDG 16.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>By making payment easier with flexible digital business models, Worldline’s Payment Acceptance, Kiosk and Digital Retail solutions enable the creation of economic value and growth for clients, via shorter time-to-market and costs reduction, thus contributing to the SDG 8.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Through its Cloud, Online and Digitization services that deliver environmental benefits including paper use reduction, travel minimization to access services or energy consumption optimization, Worldline directly contributes to the SDG 13.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Besides, as part of its CSR long-term ambition “TRUST 2020”, Worldline has committed to generate €725 m in revenue through sustainable solutions that contribute to societal and environmental progress by 2020 and has also calculated its financial contribution to the SDGs thanks to the revenue generated by its sustainable solutions.&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>From an internal perspective, Worldline’s initiatives, programs and policies related to ethics, data protection, responsible procurement, human resources, local communities development and the environment indirectly contribute to the SDG 3 “Good health and well-being”, SDG 4 “Quality Education”, SDG 5 “Gender Equality”, SDG 12 “Responsible consumption and production”, SDG 13 “Climate action” and SDG 16 “Peace, Justice and strong institutions”. For instance, as part of its “TRUST 2020” ambition and its diversity strategy, Worldline has committed to reduce the female capital gap to 0 by 2020 and has recently launched its Gender Equity program that contributes to the SDG 5 “Gender Equality”. Worldline also supports the SDG 4 “Quality education” through its learning@worldline program which aims to provide Worldline employees with the best-in-class trainings to develop their skills. Furthermore, Worldline’s environmental commitment contributes to the SDG 13 “Climate action”, especially through its offsetting program that aims to neutralize all carbon emissions related to the company’s activities by 2020. &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>A few months ago, Worldline undertook a detailed assessment in order to identify and measure its contribution to the SDGs through its sustainable offering and its internal operations. Based on its materiality matrix and in line with the SDG compass guidelines, this analysis highlighted that Worldline contributes to a large number of SDGs through its products and solutions, internal operations and value chain.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;br>&#xa;In 2015, the 193 United Nations members adopted a set of&amp;nbsp;17 SDGs to be achieved by 2030. The SDGs entered into force in January 2016 and replaced the Millennium Development Goals (MDG) adopted in 2000. These goals aim to address economic, environmental and social challenges and require collective action from the governments, the NGOs and the private sector.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>&lt;img src=&quot;/content/dam/worldline/images/press-release/sustainable-development-goals-650.png&quot;>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>In July 2016, Worldline became a signatory company of the UN Global Compact (&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.unglobalcompact.org/system/attachments/cop_2017/400321/original/Letter_Gilles_Grapinet_-_COP_Global_Compact.docx.pdf?1499361009&quot;>https://www.unglobalcompact.org/system/attachments/cop_2017/400321/original/Letter_Gilles_Grapinet_-_COP_Global_Compact.docx.pdf?1499361009&lt;/a>), a voluntary initiative launched in 2000 calling companies to align strategies and operations with 10 principles covering human rights, environment, anti-corruption and labor rights.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>One year later*, Worldline released its first Communication on Progress (COP) as part of its commitment to provide the UN with an overview of the efforts made to promote the Global Compact principles.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>In our COP, you will find how Worldline contributes and meets the UN’s principles supported by its Corporate Social Responsibility strategy that is embedded in its day-to-day operations. A special focus has been done on the measures, targets, policies and indicators around each principle.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Worldline is pleased to share with all its stakeholders the progress and efforts achieved in 2016 to implement these principles: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.unglobalcompact.org/system/attachments/cop_2017/400291/original/Worldline_Communication_on_Progress_2017.pdf?1499361009&quot;>https://www.unglobalcompact.org/system/attachments/cop_2017/400291/original/Worldline_Communication_on_Progress_2017.pdf?1499361009&lt;/a>&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>*&lt;i>Worldline’s Communication on Progress (COP) has been submitted on 7 July 2017.&lt;/i>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;>&lt;img src=&quot;/content/dam/worldline/images/press-release/united-nations-logo.png&quot;>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;blockquote>&lt;span class=&quot;block--featured--title&quot;>Gilles Grapinet, Worldline Chief Executive Officer, stated:&lt;/span> “The UN’s SDGs open a new area for Worldline to reinforce its commitment to excellence regarding sustainability. Through its “TRUST 2020” CSR long-term ambition, Worldline has already engaged in making the society and the planet more sustainable but the SDGs represent a new challenge and opportunity to further progress and to implement all the new innovative actions to create positive impacts that will contribute more widely to this global and collective action.”&amp;nbsp;&lt;/blockquote>&#xa;&lt;p>To learn more about our CSR strategy and our “TRUST 2020” ambition and commitments, please have a look to our 2016 CSR Report: &lt;a href=&quot;http://csr2016.worldline.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>http://csr2016.worldline.com/&lt;/a>&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h3>About Worldline&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>Worldline [Euronext: WLN] is the European leader in the payments and transactional services industry. Worldline delivers new-generation services, enabling its customers to offer smooth and innovative solutions to the end consumer. Key actor for B2B2C industries, with over 40 years of experience, Worldline supports and contributes to the success of all businesses and administrative services in a perpetually evolving market. Worldline offers a unique and flexible business model built around a global and growing portfolio, thus enabling end-to-end support. Worldline activities are organized around three axes: Merchant Services, Mobility &amp;amp; e-Transactional Services, Financial Services including equensWorldline. Worldline employs more than 8,700 people worldwide, with estimated pro forma revenue of more than € 1.5 billion on a yearly basis. Worldline is an Atos company. &lt;a title=&quot;https://worldline.com&quot; href=&quot;https://worldline.com&quot;>worldline.com&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h3>Worldline Press Contacts&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>Teamfluence : Tiphaine Hecketsweiler&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Email: &lt;a title=&quot;mailto:th@teamfluence.eu&quot; href=&quot;mailto:th@teamfluence.eu&quot;>th@teamfluence.eu&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                        textIsRich="true"/>
                </column1>
            </grid>
        </content>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
