<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:contextHubPath="/etc/cloudsettings/default/contexthub"
        cq:contextHubSegmentsPath="/etc/segmentation/contexthub"
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2017-11-27T15:58:56.315+01:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="a598986"
        cq:tags="[blog:csr,blog:corporate]"
        cq:template="/apps/gotomarket/templates/blogarticle"
        jcr:description="In 2015, the 193 United Nations members launched the 17 Sustainable Development Goals (SDGs), a universal, global and inclusive action and roadmap to end poverty, protect the planet and ensure prosperity and peace for all by 2030. The SDGs entered into force in January 2016 and replaced the Millennium Development Goals (MDGs) adopted in 2000. These goals aim to address economic, environmental and social challenges and require collective actions from governments, NGOs and the private sector. As a European leader in the payment and transactional services industry, Worldline is convinced it has a significant role to play to contribute to the achievement of these goals through its sustainable offers, its internal operations and its TRUST 2020 CSR long-term program."
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-11-27T15:33:14.715+01:00"
        jcr:lastModifiedBy="a598986"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:lockable,mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Worldline reinforces its commitment to sustainability by contributing to the United Nations’ Sustainable Development Goals"
        jcr:uuid="547591f2-4721-48f1-9212-6cd3d695eb38"
        sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/pages/blogarticle"
        authorImage="/content/dam/worldline/images/blog/author/wl.png"
        authorName="Worldline"
        authorText="Corporate Social Responsibility"
        categories="[category:news]"
        categories_x0040_TypeHint="String[]"
        color="#ffffff"
        creationDate="{Date}2017-09-06T15:44:00.000+02:00"
        hideInNav="false"
        imagePath="/content/dam/worldline/images/blog/header/build-your-career-header-v2.jpg"
        isExternalContactUsUrl="false"
        isExternalJoinUsUrl="false"
        isStickyContactHidden="false"
        noExtentionContactUs="false"
        noExtentionJoinUs="false"
        showbrand="false"
        showinfostrip="false"
        title="Worldline reinforces&#xd;&#xa;its commitment to sustainability&#xd;&#xa;by contributing to the United Nations’ Sustainable Development Goals">
        <head
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/head"/>
        <headlibs
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/headlibs"/>
        <header
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/header">
            <leftnavigation
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/leftnavigation"
                iconClass="iconClass2"/>
            <rightnavigation
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/rightnavigation"
                iconClass="iconClass2">
                <countrylistdropdown
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/countrylistdropdown"/>
                <languagedropdown
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/languagedropdown"/>
            </rightnavigation>
            <mainnav
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/mainnav"/>
            <infostrip
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/infostrip"/>
            <breadcrumbblog
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/breadcrumbblog"/>
        </header>
        <headerblog
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/headerblog"/>
        <singleauthor
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/singleauthor"/>
        <prshare
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/prshare"/>
        <stayintouch
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/stayintouch"/>
        <footer
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/footer">
            <sitemap
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/sitemap"/>
            <followus
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/followus"/>
            <newsletterform
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/newsletterform"/>
        </footer>
        <footlibs
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/footlibs"/>
        <copyright
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/copyright"/>
        <content
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/parsys">
            <richtext
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-09-07T14:33:40.318+02:00"
                jcr:createdBy="a646217"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-11-27T15:58:56.310+01:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="a598986"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/content/richtext"
                text="&lt;p>In 2015, the 193 United Nations members launched the 17 Sustainable Development Goals (SDGs), a universal, global and inclusive action and roadmap to end poverty, protect the planet and ensure prosperity and peace for all by 2030. The SDGs entered into force in January 2016 and replaced the Millennium Development Goals (MDGs) adopted in 2000. These goals aim to address economic, environmental and social challenges and require collective actions from governments, NGOs and the private sector. As a European leader in the payment and transactional services industry, Worldline is convinced it has a significant role to play to contribute to the achievement of these goals through its sustainable offers, its internal operations and its TRUST 2020 CSR long-term program.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Discover in the following article why and how Worldline contributes to the SDGs while creating sustainable value for its stakeholders.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;blockquote>&lt;span class=&quot;block--featured--title&quot;>Gilles Grapinet:&lt;/span> “The UN’s SDGs open a new area for Worldline to reinforce its commitment to excellence regarding sustainability. Through its “TRUST 2020” CSR long-term ambition, Worldline has already engaged in making the society and the planet more sustainable but the SDGs represent a new challenge and opportunity to further progress and to implement all the new innovative actions to create positive impacts that will contribute more widely to this global and collective action.”&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;/blockquote>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h3 style=&quot;color: #0066A1;&quot;>Why Worldline has decided to commit to the SDGs:&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>Several studies have already demonstrated that digital technology represents a key catalyst for sustainable progress. This is why, as a key actor of the digital transformation, we are strongly determined to play a significant role in helping to achieve the SDGs by embedding them in our business strategy and Corporate Social Responsibility (CSR) approach. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>According to the GeSI (Global e-Sustainability Initiative) report “How digital solutions will drive progress towards the sustainable development goals”, IT will be a key enabler in achieving each SDG through e-healthcare, e-education, smart agriculture, smart building, e-government, e-banking, traffic control, smart energy or connectivity solutions. Thanks to our high innovation capabilities to design and offer sustainable solutions combined with our CSR commitments related to availability and security of platforms, data protection, ethics, responsible procurement, health &amp;amp; well-being, equity and the environment, we are well-positioned to address digital challenges that will contribute to achieving the SDGs.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h3 style=&quot;color: #0066A1;&quot;>How Worldline contributes to the SDGs:&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>Based on this observation, we decided to support the United Nations’ SDGs and undertook a detailed assessment in order to identify and measure our contribution to each SDG through a two-dimensional mapping approach:&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;span class=&quot;styled&quot;>On one end, through our offering’s sustainability;&lt;/span>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;span class=&quot;styled&quot;>On the other end, through our internal operations and our value chain.&lt;/span>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>This exhaustive analysis highlighted that we overall contribute to 13 SDGs.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;u>Our main external contributions to the SDGs through our sustainable offers:&lt;/u>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;u>Our main internal contributions to the SDGs through our value chain and internal operations:&lt;/u>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>However, based on the most material CSR topics for our stakeholders and for our business activities, and in line with the SDGs compass guidelines, we have decided to concentrate our efforts on the 5 most relevant SDGs on which we have the most significant impact and can maximize our contribution:&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;span class=&quot;styled&quot;>To promote peace, justice and strong institutions (SDG 16),&lt;/span>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;span class=&quot;styled&quot;>To ensure a decent work and economic growth (SDG 8),&lt;/span>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;span class=&quot;styled&quot;>To be involved in climate action (SDG 13),&lt;/span>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;span class=&quot;styled&quot;>To ensure responsible production and consumption (SDG 12),&lt;/span>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;span class=&quot;styled&quot;>To ensure inclusive and equitable quality education (SDG 4).&lt;/span>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>In addition, we also have a particular impact on 2 complementary SDGs, SDG 3 “Good health and well-being” and SDG 5 “Gender Equality” covering two areas in which Worldline is highly involved through its wellbeing@worldline and Gender Equity programs.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>And last but not least, we also contribute to the SDGs through our TRUST 2020 CSR long-term program that aims to put sustainability at the very heart of our strategy and ecosystem and to develop trust-based relationships with our stakeholders. The matrix below illustrates Worldline’s level of contribution to each SDG based on its TRUST 2020 commitments.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h3 style=&quot;color: #0066A1;&quot;>How our contributions to the SDGs create sustainable value for our stakeholders:&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: 0.8125rem;&quot;>The SDGs represent a new reference framework that creates a universal language and a common tool for sustainable development we can use with our stakeholders while taking into account their own economic, social and environmental challenges and expectations.&lt;/span>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>We can therefore better demonstrate the sustainable value we bring to our stakeholders by strengthening our “outside-in” vision and ensuring greater clarity and consistency of our actions.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>As reinforcing value for clients through sustainable and innovative solutions is a key challenge in our CSR strategy, we have assessed the impacts of our solutions and products on the SDGs. This has showcased that our sustainable offers provide our clients with benefits that mainly contribute to SDG 8 “Decent work and economic growth”, SDG 9 “Industry, innovation and infrastructure”, SDG 10 “Reduced inequalities”, SDG 13 “Climate action” and SDG 16 “Peace, justice and strong institutions”.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Besides, as part of our TRUST 2020 CSR long-term ambition, we have committed to generate €725M in revenue through sustainable solutions that contribute to societal and environmental progress by 2020. In light of this, we have calculated our financial contribution to the SDGs thanks to the revenue generated by our sustainable solutions. The diagram below depicts the distribution of our current sustainable revenue (€586M in 2016) on each SDG and highlights the 5 SDGs on which we have the greatest financial impact:&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Additionally, from an internal perspective, our employees can better understand and participate in initiatives that directly benefit their development and well-being via SDG 3 “Good health and well-being”, SDG 4 “Quality Education and SDG 5 “Gender Equality”. Moreover, the SDGs enable our employees to more easily understand the link between societal issues and Worldline’s CSR commitments.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>To a broader extent, all our stakeholders in public organisms, NGOs and citizens are more easily able to identify, assess and position Worldline regarding its initiatives, programs and policies related to key SDGs challenges: ethics, data protection, responsible procurement, human resources, local communities development and the environment; Initiatives which indirectly contribute to the SDG 12 “Responsible consumption and production”, SDG 13 “Climate action” and SDG 16 “Peace, Justice and strong institutions”.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h3 style=&quot;color: #0066A1;&quot;>By putting the SDGs at the core of our CSR strategy, we proactively demonstrate our willingness to take into account and to contribute to the resolution of societal issues and to sustainable development. It implies the cartography of societal risks with related actions taken to reduce these risks. By doing so, we fit in a long-term perspective and give to investors, and more widely to all our stakeholders, a framework that clarifies and upholds our strong commitment to sustainable development.&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                textIsRich="true"/>
        </content>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
