<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:contextHubPath="/etc/cloudsettings/default/contexthub"
        cq:contextHubSegmentsPath="/etc/segmentation/contexthub"
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2017-11-27T17:48:21.252+01:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="fr20437"
        cq:lastReplicated="{Date}2017-11-29T17:32:28.508+01:00"
        cq:lastReplicatedBy="fr20437"
        cq:lastReplicationAction="Activate"
        cq:tags="[article:general]"
        cq:template="/apps/gotomarket/templates/releasearticle"
        jcr:description="London, 27 July 2017 – Worldline, European leader in the payment and transactional services industry, announces a new three-year deal with Whitbread to continue providing Business Account Card services at its Premier Inn hotels and restaurants. The contract extension is valued at £16.7m."
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-11-27T17:48:21.248+01:00"
        jcr:lastModifiedBy="fr20437"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Whitbread and Worldline sign new contract for Business Account Card services at Premier Inn"
        jcr:uuid="0f181791-7332-4c6b-82fc-ba0e8212ed74"
        sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/pages/releasearticle"
        categories_x0040_TypeHint="String[]"
        creationDate="{Date}2017-07-27T14:00:00.000+02:00"
        hideInNav="false"
        imagePath="/content/dam/gotomarket/uploads/bg-header-industries.jpg"
        isExternalContactUsUrl="false"
        isExternalJoinUsUrl="false"
        isStickyContactHidden="false"
        keywords="Whitbread, Worldline,  new contract, Business Account Card services, Premier Inn"
        keywords_x0040_TypeHint="String[]"
        noExtentionContactUs="false"
        noExtentionJoinUs="false"
        showbrand="false"
        showinfostrip="false">
        <head
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/head"/>
        <headlibs
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/headlibs"/>
        <header
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/header">
            <leftnavigation
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/leftnavigation"
                iconClass="iconClass2"/>
            <rightnavigation
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/rightnavigation"
                iconClass="iconClass2">
                <countrylistdropdown
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/countrylistdropdown"/>
                <languagedropdown
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/languagedropdown"/>
            </rightnavigation>
            <mainnav
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/mainnav"/>
            <infostrip
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/infostrip"/>
            <breadcrumb
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/breadcrumb"/>
        </header>
        <headerpage
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/headerpage"/>
        <releasetitle
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/releasetitle"/>
        <key
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/parsys">
            <releasekeymessages
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/releasekeymessages"/>
        </key>
        <releasedescription
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/releasedescription"/>
        <prshare
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/prshare"/>
        <footer
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/footer">
            <sitemap
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/sitemap"/>
            <followus
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/followus"/>
            <newsletterform
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/newsletterform"/>
        </footer>
        <footlibs
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/footlibs"/>
        <copyright
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/copyright"/>
        <content
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/parsys">
            <grid
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-08-18T17:30:12.069+02:00"
                jcr:createdBy="fr20437"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-08-18T17:30:12.069+02:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="fr20437"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/layout/grid">
                <column1
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/parsys">
                    <richtext
                        jcr:created="{Date}2017-08-18T17:30:32.273+02:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="fr20437"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-09-27T20:04:40.134+02:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="fr20437"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/content/richtext"
                        text="&lt;h3>&lt;span class=&quot;block--featured--title&quot;>&lt;/span>Three-year contract extension positions WL Business Account Card for cross market growth&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>London, 27 July 2017 – Worldline, European leader in the payment and transactional services industry, announces a new three-year deal with Whitbread to continue providing Business Account Card services at its Premier Inn hotels and restaurants. The contract extension is valued at £16.7m.&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xa;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br>&#xa;The Premier Inn’s WL Business Account Card scheme makes it easy for business travelers to pay for meals and accommodation, and ensures efficient and transparent cost control for their employer.&amp;nbsp; lt allows spending limits to be put on employees’ cards, provides financial controllers with a full breakdown of card usage, and employees don’t need to worry about submitting and processing receipts. Take up of the scheme has been impressive since its launch more than 10 years ago. The WL Business Account Card scheme now contributes some 25% of annual revenues for Premier Inn hotels and restaurants.&lt;br>&#xa;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br>&#xa;The End-to-end WL Business Account Card services are designed and built by Worldline for companies in any sector wanting to provide account card support for their business customers, whatever type and size of organisation they represent. Crucial capabilities include customer on-boarding, credit (insurance and checking), debt management, card production, payment processing, account/customer management, and transaction processing.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;blockquote>&lt;span class=&quot;block--featured--title&quot;>Karen Plumb, Director of Demand, said: &lt;/span>“Our business customers want a payments service that is easy to use and efficient to manage. We know how important that is when they choose hotels and restaurants, and we’re delighted that the WL Business Account Card scheme helps many business people select Premier Inn hotels and restaurants. When we considered a partner for our Business Account Card scheme for the next three years, it didn’t take us long to appoint Worldline. We have a successful relationship over many years, and we see Worldline as a strong technology partner.”&lt;/blockquote>&#xa;&lt;blockquote>&lt;span class=&quot;block--featured--title&quot;>Lisa Coleman, Chief Executive Officer, Worldline said:&lt;/span> “I am delighted that Worldline has been able to secure this contract extension with Whitbread. It marks the successful operation of the Premier Inn’s Business Account Card scheme over many years, and delivery of a significant revenue stream for Whitbread. WL Business Account Card services can be developed for our customers in many different sectors to help their business users control costs and provide employees with a simple way to pay for day-to-day expenses.”&lt;/blockquote>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h3>Worldline Press Contact&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>3x1 Public Relations&lt;br>&#xa;Karen Halley / Jackie McColl&lt;br>&#xa;Email: &lt;a title=&quot;mailto:khalley@3x1.com&quot; href=&quot;mailto:khalley@3x1.com&quot;>khalley@3x1.com&lt;/a> / &lt;a title=&quot;mailto:jmccoll@3x1.com&quot; href=&quot;mailto:jmccoll@3x1.com&quot;>jmccoll@3x1.com&lt;/a>&lt;br>&#xa;0131 225 7700 / 0141 221 0707&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h3>About Worldline&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>Worldline [Euronext: WLN] is the European leader in the payments and transactional services industry. Worldline delivers new-generation services, enabling its customers to offer smooth and innovative solutions to the end consumer. Key actor for B2B2C industries, with nearly 45 years of experience, Worldline supports and contributes to the success of all businesses and administrative services in a perpetually evolving market. Worldline offers a unique and flexible business model built around a global and growing portfolio, thus enabling end-to-end support. Worldline activities are organized around three axes: Merchant Services, Mobility &amp;amp; e-Transactional Services and Financial Services including equensWorldline. Worldline employs more than 8,700 people worldwide, with estimated pro forma revenue of more than € 1.5 billion on a yearly basis. Worldline is an Atos company. &lt;a title=&quot;https://worldline.com&quot; href=&quot;https://worldline.com&quot;>worldline.com&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h3>About Whitbread PLC&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>Whitbread PLC is the owner of the UK’s favourite hotel chain, Premier Inn and the UK’s favourite coffee shop, Costa, as well as restaurant brands, Beefeater, Brewers Fayre and Table Table.&lt;br>&#xa;Whitbread is ranked no. 8 in the Sunday Times Best Big Companies to Work For list and employs around 50,000 people in over 2,400* outlets across the UK, serving over 28 million customers every month. Whitbread has ambitious growth plans to increase the number of Premier Inn UK rooms to around 85,000 and to achieve global system sales of around £2.5bn for Costa by 2020. At Whitbread we are committed to being a force for good in the communities in which we operate. Our Sustainability programme, ‘Force for Good’ is focused on enabling people to live and work well and is built around three pillars of Opportunity, Community and Responsibility. In the year ended 2 March 2017, Whitbread PLC reported an 8.2%† increase in Group Revenue to £3.1 billion and Underlying Profit before tax of £565 million up 6.2%†.Whitbread PLC is listed on the London Stock Exchange and is a constituent of the FTSE 100. It is also a member of the FTSE4Good Index.&lt;br>&#xa;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br>&#xa;*excludes Costa Franchise stores and Costa Express&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                        textIsRich="true"/>
                </column1>
            </grid>
        </content>
        <image
            jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-08-22T16:00:29.531+04:00"
            jcr:lastModifiedBy="admin"
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"/>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
