<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:contextHubPath="/etc/cloudsettings/default/contexthub"
        cq:contextHubSegmentsPath="/etc/segmentation/contexthub"
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2017-11-30T09:59:58.179+01:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="a598986"
        cq:lastReplicated="{Date}2017-11-30T10:00:28.964+01:00"
        cq:lastReplicatedBy="a598986"
        cq:lastReplicationAction="Activate"
        cq:tags="[blog:digital-transformation,blog:retail,blog:epayment,blog:innovation,blog:customer-experience]"
        cq:template="/apps/gotomarket/templates/blogarticle"
        jcr:description="In our 2nd post on Samsung’s Innovation Week, we focus on our featured solutions in the Parisian pop-up store. Julien Decoster shares their functionalities and how they can change physical stores."
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-11-30T09:59:58.171+01:00"
        jcr:lastModifiedBy="a598986"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Samsung Innovation Week – Part 2 "
        jcr:uuid="557a8efd-6bab-44b0-84aa-05f857bd0cfd"
        sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/pages/blogarticle"
        authorImage="/content/dam/worldline/images/blog/author/julien-decoster80.jpg"
        authorName="Julien Decoster"
        authorText="Head of Business Development, Merchant Services"
        categories="[category:solutions]"
        categories_x0040_TypeHint="String[]"
        hideInNav="false"
        imagePath="/content/dam/worldline/images/blog/header/samsung-innovation-week-700x329.png"
        isExternalContactUsUrl="false"
        isExternalJoinUsUrl="false"
        isStickyContactHidden="false"
        noExtentionContactUs="false"
        noExtentionJoinUs="false"
        showbrand="false"
        showinfostrip="false"
        title="Samsung Innovation Week&#xd;&#xa;Part 2 ">
        <head
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/head"/>
        <headlibs
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/headlibs"/>
        <header
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/header">
            <leftnavigation
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/leftnavigation"
                iconClass="iconClass2"/>
            <rightnavigation
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/rightnavigation"
                iconClass="iconClass2">
                <countrylistdropdown
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/countrylistdropdown"/>
                <languagedropdown
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/languagedropdown"/>
            </rightnavigation>
            <mainnav
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/mainnav"/>
            <infostrip
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/infostrip"/>
            <breadcrumbblog
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/breadcrumbblog"/>
        </header>
        <headerblog
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/headerblog"/>
        <singleauthor
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/singleauthor"/>
        <prshare
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/prshare"/>
        <stayintouch
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/stayintouch"/>
        <footer
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/footer">
            <sitemap
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/sitemap"/>
            <followus
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/followus"/>
            <newsletterform
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/newsletterform"/>
        </footer>
        <footlibs
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/footlibs"/>
        <copyright
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/copyright"/>
        <content
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/parsys">
            <richtext
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-09-12T17:54:20.263+02:00"
                jcr:createdBy="a101309"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-09-12T17:55:33.372+02:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="a101309"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/content/richtext"
                text="&lt;h2>Hi Julien, what do you work on at Worldline?&lt;/h2>&#xa;&lt;p>Hello, I am in charge of pre-sales in our Merchant Services &amp;amp; Terminals business unit in which I work mainly on retail. Since the beginning of our partnership with Samsung, our focus has been on POS (ed: Point Of Sale) digitization to meet the growing challenges tied to omni-channels. We also work on the development of e-commerce and m-commerce sites.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h2>When did you join us and what were you doing before?&lt;/h2>&#xa;&lt;p>I joined Worldline in 2000. I started working in the Banking Department before joining the Media Department. I joined Merchant Services &amp;amp; Terminals in 2011.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h2>We participated in the Samsung Innovation Week in France; can you tell us more about this project?&lt;/h2>&#xa;&lt;p>With this event, Samsung wanted to showcase a physical and digital store, and build tomorrow’s buying journey. Samsung, being mainly a device manufacturer, called on its partners to help create this digital experience and to provide services solutions for their devices. Worldline and Samsung being partners for the past two years, we participated in this event with some of our solutions.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h2>As you just mentioned, we demoed some of our products in this pop-up shop, can you explain their features, their added values and their impacts on the user experience?&lt;/h2>&#xa;"
                textIsRich="true"/>
            <richtext_430689633
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-09-12T17:55:42.671+02:00"
                jcr:createdBy="a101309"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-09-12T17:56:13.752+02:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="a101309"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/content/richtext"
                text="&lt;h2>Promowall&lt;/h2>&#xa;&lt;p>video&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                textIsRich="true"/>
            <richtext_650349816
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-09-12T17:56:20.405+02:00"
                jcr:createdBy="a101309"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-09-12T17:56:45.896+02:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="a101309"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/content/richtext"
                text="&lt;p>This solution was integrated on a 75” touchscreen and displayed promotional coupons. Customers were able to directly interact with it. This wall is ideal for shopping centers but can also be used in other locations (ed: we had one on display in the Barcelona airport during the recent Mobile World Congress).&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>The consumer interacts with the Promowall, via its fluid navigation system, by selecting relevant offers based on his preferences, such as clothes or electronics, for example. When the consumer finds an interesting promotion, he can download it directly in his promotion-dedicated digital wallet on his smartphone. This specific wallet application allows the customer to scan the selected promotion’s QR code, store it on his smartphone to then use it either in store or online. The number of coupons is limited per promotion in order to encourage download and redemption, and the use window is limited as well. By combining this solution with indoor localization, the downloaded coupon can guide consumers to the store where it can be used, through their smartphone.&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                textIsRich="true"/>
            <richtext_1310555294
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-09-12T17:56:54.904+02:00"
                jcr:createdBy="a101309"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-09-12T17:57:51.543+02:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="a101309"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/content/richtext"
                text="&lt;p>&lt;img src=&quot;/content/dam/worldline/images/blog/graphics/smbm-300x300.png&quot; class=&quot;img-right&quot;>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>This solution was also displayed on a Samsung 75” screen and allowed us to create a virtual shelf. Although this solution does not use the touch capabilities of the screen, consumers can interact with each displayed product, as if they are in front of a physical shelf, via their smartphone. Indeed, through our dedicated smartphone application, consumers use augmented reality to get additional information, such as labels and prices, and thus interact with the displayed products. Additionally, this solution allows consumers to add the scanned product, or products, directly into their virtual basket. We pushed this solution even further for this event by offering customized content to be displayed depending on different consumer profiles. We tied a Samsung phone to one consumer profile and a Samsung tablet to a different one. A certain branded bottle of sparkling water was displayed on the virtual shelf and, depending on the used device, the user would see the original bottle, and its detailed information, or one from a competitor, because identified as this profile’s preferred brand.&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                textIsRich="true"/>
            <richtext_1617457303
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-09-12T17:57:58.578+02:00"
                jcr:createdBy="a101309"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-09-12T17:59:18.716+02:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="a101309"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/content/richtext"
                text="&lt;p>&lt;img src=&quot;/content/dam/worldline/images/blog/graphics/mobile-seller-300x300.png&quot; class=&quot;img-left&quot;>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h2>Mobile Seller with Yomani (ed: payment terminal):&lt;/h2>&#xa;&lt;p>The goal of Mobile Seller is to allow sales agents to offer customers an ultra-personalized experience. Indeed, today, some customers have better understanding of products than some agents. In this context, Mobile Seller gives a level of power back to sales agents, in order to better know their customers and to better support them in their buying journey. It also provides them with detailed information on products. Mobile Seller is used on a tablet on which sales agents can find all necessary information to support customers. It all begins with the personalized welcome, thanks to the identification of the customer's smartphone through beacons installed in the store, when he enters the shop. The sales agent then receives a notification on his tablet and is presented with the customer records (ed: name and purchase history, for example). Our Mobile Seller solution also allows the agent to access product information and related products, for cross-selling, via the bar code scanning functionality of the tablet. Thus, the agent can better advise his customer and even deliver increasingly personalized advices based on the customer’s preferences, available on his records hosted on Mobile Seller.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>For our Innovation Week demo, Mobile Seller was also set up to allow agents to recover an online cart, which did not go through final check-out, from a customer who visited the website prior to visiting the physical shop.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>By combining our Yomani payment terminal with our Mobile Seller solution, we can transfer the payment from a standard register to a tablet, and thus offer a new in-store fully mobile shopping experience. As part of this event, Samsung wanted to highlight its new NFC payment solution, Samsung Pay, and therefore our demo allowed users to pay for their purchases with a simple tap of their Samsung smartphone on our payment terminal connected to our Mobile Seller application. This demonstration also included digital signage functionality through the integration of tax refunds’ management.&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;br>&#xa;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                textIsRich="true"/>
            <richtext_1541878487
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-09-12T17:59:26.173+02:00"
                jcr:createdBy="a101309"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-09-12T18:00:35.834+02:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="a101309"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/content/richtext"
                text="&lt;h2>What are the benefits of these solutions for consumers and for merchants?&lt;/h2>&#xa;&lt;p>We are working on different buying journeys for the store of the future and, therefore, on many different customer profiles. We presented two of these journeys during the Innovation Week, one for the autonomous customer and the other for the customer accompanied by the sales agent.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>The autonomous customer can interact through his smartphone with various digital terminals installed throughout his journey in the store. Through these interactions, the customer gets personalized information within the store without the assistance of a salesperson.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>We often speak of the &amp;quot;phygital&amp;quot; experience (ed: cross between the physical and the digital worlds) when it comes to the use case of the customer accompanied by the salesperson. In this context, the agent uses digital media to better serve the customer and provide him with a high-value personalized experience.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>The common benefits for both models are the improved customer experience and the reduction of in-store wait time, thanks to, either, NFC payment or, alternatively, to Mobile Seller.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>For merchants, these solutions will allow them to sell more through a more personalized service which is, in the consumers’ eyes, a high added value. In addition, these services and interactions on digital terminals generate data. Said data will help merchants manage their store and their stock, and thus better understand the different profiles of their customers, all in order to better serve them.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h2>Thank you for your time today. I will leave you with one final question: we live in a hyper connected digital world and, suddenly, you find yourself stranded on a desert island, which electronic product do you have to have with you?&lt;/h2>&#xa;&lt;p>My smartphone, which I cannot live without, but I will need a network of course.&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;br>&#xa;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                textIsRich="true"/>
        </content>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
