<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:contextHubPath="/etc/cloudsettings/default/contexthub"
        cq:contextHubSegmentsPath="/etc/segmentation/contexthub"
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2017-11-27T18:05:01.413+01:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="fr20437"
        cq:lastReplicated="{Date}2017-11-27T18:13:25.503+01:00"
        cq:lastReplicatedBy="fr20437"
        cq:lastReplicationAction="Activate"
        cq:tags="[article:]"
        cq:template="/apps/gotomarket/templates/releasearticle"
        jcr:description="Frankfurt/Main, September 22, 2016 – Worldline [Euronext: WLN], the European leader in the payment and transactional services sector and Consorsbank, part of major French bank, BNP Paribas, have extended their partnership to the end of 2021. As a partner, Worldline takes over the issuing processing for Visa cards, as well as cardholder services. The early contract extension for a further five years confirms the successful and fair cooperation between Consorsbank and Worldline."
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-11-27T18:05:01.409+01:00"
        jcr:lastModifiedBy="fr20437"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Worldline and Consorsbank extend their partnership for a further five years"
        jcr:uuid="56497cab-2eb4-4943-b3a3-799753184d99"
        sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/pages/releasearticle"
        brand="worldline"
        categories="[article:]"
        categories_x0040_TypeHint="String[]"
        creationDate="{Date}2016-09-22T18:04:00.000+02:00"
        hideInNav="false"
        imagePath="/content/dam/gotomarket/uploads/bg-header-industries.jpg"
        isExternalContactUsUrl="false"
        isExternalJoinUsUrl="false"
        isStickyContactHidden="false"
        keywords="Worldline, Consorsbank, partnership &#xd;&#xa;"
        noExtentionContactUs="false"
        noExtentionJoinUs="false"
        showbrand="false"
        showinfostrip="false">
        <head
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/head"/>
        <headlibs
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/headlibs"/>
        <header
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/header">
            <leftnavigation
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/leftnavigation"
                iconClass="iconClass2"/>
            <rightnavigation
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/rightnavigation"
                iconClass="iconClass2">
                <countrylistdropdown
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/countrylistdropdown"/>
                <languagedropdown
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/languagedropdown"/>
            </rightnavigation>
            <mainnav
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/mainnav"/>
            <infostrip
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/infostrip"/>
            <breadcrumb
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/breadcrumb"/>
        </header>
        <headerpage
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/headerpage"/>
        <releasetitle
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/releasetitle"/>
        <key
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/parsys">
            <releasekeymessages
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/releasekeymessages"/>
        </key>
        <releasedescription
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/releasedescription"/>
        <prshare
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/prshare"/>
        <footer
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/footer">
            <sitemap
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/sitemap"/>
            <followus
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/followus"/>
            <newsletterform
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/newsletterform"/>
        </footer>
        <footlibs
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/footlibs"/>
        <copyright
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/copyright"/>
        <content
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/parsys">
            <grid
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-08-28T14:08:31.820+02:00"
                jcr:createdBy="a646217"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-08-28T14:08:31.820+02:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="a646217"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/layout/grid">
                <column1
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/parsys">
                    <richtext
                        jcr:created="{Date}2017-08-28T14:08:39.814+02:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="a646217"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-08-28T14:11:08.065+02:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="a646217"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/content/richtext"
                        text="&lt;p>&lt;b>Frankfurt/Main, September 22, 2016 – Worldline [Euronext: WLN], the European leader in the payment and transactional services sector and Consorsbank, part of major French bank, BNP Paribas, have extended their partnership to the end of 2021. As a partner, Worldline takes over the issuing processing for Visa cards, as well as cardholder services. The early contract extension for a further five years confirms the successful and fair cooperation between Consorsbank and Worldline.&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Since 2007, Worldline has been the processing provider for Consorsbank. Despite the issuing processing that involves authorization, as well as card and pin management, Worldline also provides parts of the cardholder services. This includes a 24h call centre service, fraud and risk management and chargeback services.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Consorsbank is one of the fastest growing card issuers in German-speaking countries. In the first quarter of 2016, Consorsbank expanded their credit card portfolio by adding a Visa Gold Card programme including extensive additional services.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;blockquote>&lt;span class=&quot;block--featured--title&quot;>Wolf Kunisch, Managing Director of Financial Processing &amp;amp; Software Licensing and for Germany &amp;amp; CEE at Worldline:&lt;/span>&lt;b> &lt;/b>“The early contract extension with Consorsbank confirms our successful cooperation, as well as the satisfaction of the customer. It is our aim to support Consorsbank’s transformation from a direct bank to a digital bank, through our services.”&lt;/blockquote>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;blockquote>&lt;span class=&quot;block--featured--title&quot;>Ulrich Zimmermann, Director of Banking Operations at Consorsbank, adds:&lt;/span>&lt;b> &lt;/b>“Worldline has been our partner for almost ten years, and we appreciate the high flexibility. The payment and credit card market is changing constantly. Through Worldline’s support we are able to react to these changes flexibly and immediately. Our customers are able to use services faster and more transparently without changing mediums. For that, they will soon be able to block their bank cards or conduct any other business transactions directly via their smartphones, for example. Banking wherever, whenever, on any device and in real time - that is our goal, and the services and technology that Worldline provides have convinced us in this regard.”&lt;/blockquote>&#xa;&lt;h3>About Worldline&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>Worldline [Euronext: WLN] is the European leader in the payments and transactional services industry. Worldline delivers new-generation services, enabling its customers to offer smooth and innovative solutions to the end consumer. Key actor for B2B2C industries, with over 40 years of experience, Worldline supports and contributes to the success of all businesses and administrative services in a perpetually evolving market. Worldline offers a unique and flexible business model built around a global and growing portfolio, thus enabling end-to-end support. Worldline activities are organized around three axes: Merchant Services &amp;amp; Terminals, Mobility &amp;amp; e-Transactional Services, Financial Processing &amp;amp; Software Licensing. Worldline employs more than 7,300 people worldwide and generated 1.22 billion euros revenues in 2015. Worldline is an Atos company. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.worldline.com&quot;>www.worldline.com&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h3>About Consorsbank&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Consorsbank&lt;/b> is part of major French bank, BNP Paribas. Up to December 2014, Consorsbank operated under the name Cortal Consors. The German headquarters of its direct bank is located in Nuremberg. With a comprehensive offer of financial products and services, Consorsbank is one of the leading direct banks. Consorsbank wishes to apply the rules of digital life to bank services, as well as develop the future of banking together with their customers.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h3>&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bnpparibas.com/en&quot;>About BNP Paribas&lt;/a>&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>BNP Paribas&lt;/b> is a leading bank in Europe with an international reach. It has a presence in 75 countries, with more than 189,000 employees, including more than 146,000 in Europe. The Group has key positions in its three main activities: Domestic Markets, International Financial Services (whose retail banking networks and financial services are covered by Retail Banking &amp;amp; Services) and Corporate &amp;amp; Institutional Banking, which serves two client franchises: corporate clients and institutional investors. The Group helps all its clients (individuals, community associations, entrepreneurs, SMEs, corporate and institutional clients) to realize their projects through solutions spanning financing, investment, savings and protection insurance. In Europe, the Group has four domestic markets (Belgium, France, Italy and Luxembourg), and BNP Paribas Personal Finance is the leader in consumer lending. BNP Paribas is rolling out its integrated retail banking model in Mediterranean countries, Turkey, Eastern Europe and a large network in the western part of the United States. BNP Paribas is also a European leader in its Corporate &amp;amp; Institutional Banking and International Financial Services activities, and has a strong presence in the Americas as well as a solid and fast-growing business in Asia-Pacific. The BNP Paribas Group has been active in Germany since 1947 and has been successfully positioned across the market with 13 operational companies. There are 5,000 employees in 19 locations to serve private clients, companies and institutional clients. BNP Paribas’ broad range of products and services is in line with the range of a universal bank.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h3>Worldline Press Contacts&lt;b>&lt;/b>&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;table width=&quot;653&quot; cellspacing=&quot;0&quot; cellpadding=&quot;0&quot; border=&quot;0&quot;>&#xa;&lt;tbody>&lt;tr>&lt;td width=&quot;653&quot; valign=&quot;top&quot;>&lt;p>&lt;b>Cendrella Bourjaili&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Email : cendrella.bourjaili@worldline.com&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;/td>&#xa;&lt;/tr>&lt;tr>&lt;td width=&quot;653&quot; valign=&quot;top&quot;>&lt;p>&lt;b>Aressy RP&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Sarah Ousahla – Camille Pan&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Email&amp;nbsp;: &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:worldline@aressy-rp.com&quot;>worldline@aressy-rp.com&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>+33 (0)1 85 76 30 52 – +33 (0)1 85 76 12 04&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;/td>&#xa;&lt;/tr>&lt;/tbody>&lt;/table>&#xa;"
                        textIsRich="true"/>
                </column1>
            </grid>
        </content>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
