<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:contextHubPath="/etc/cloudsettings/default/contexthub"
        cq:contextHubSegmentsPath="/etc/segmentation/contexthub"
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2017-11-27T18:15:05.764+01:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="fr20437"
        cq:lastReplicated="{Date}2017-11-27T18:27:13.728+01:00"
        cq:lastReplicatedBy="fr20437"
        cq:lastReplicationAction="Activate"
        cq:tags="[article:general]"
        cq:template="/apps/gotomarket/templates/releasearticle"
        jcr:description="Frankfurt/Main, 12. February 2015 - Survival in the Internet age - for retail not an easy task. The rapid proliferation of smartphones and tablets has changed consumer behavior. Consumers today decide for themselves where, when and what channel to use when they are researching, shopping or getting in touch with a brand. Worldline [EUR Next: WLN] the European leader in payment and transaction services, has developed tailored products and solutions to enable retailers to connect their physical stores to the retail world. At EuroCIS 2015 in Düsseldorf (February 24 to 26) interested parties can learn more at booth A39 in Hall 9, about how with the help of the &quot;Worldline Promotion Wall&quot;, the &quot;Worldline cash register&quot; and the application &quot;Scan me Buy me&quot; they can improve the shopping experience for their customers. &#xd;&#xa;"
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-08-25T18:04:38.772+02:00"
        jcr:lastModifiedBy="a101309"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="EuroCIS 2015: Back to the store - Worldline improves shopping experience in retail and supports cross-channel strategies"
        jcr:uuid="64b9b9f9-0e3e-4784-9410-a8c3eec668d5"
        sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/pages/releasearticle"
        brand="worldline"
        categories_x0040_TypeHint="String[]"
        creationDate="{Date}2015-02-12T08:00:00.000+01:00"
        hideInNav="false"
        imagePath="/content/dam/gotomarket/uploads/bg-header-industries.jpg"
        keywords="press, worldline, EuroCIS,"
        onTime="{Date}2016-02-12T08:00:00.000+01:00"
        showbrand="false"
        showinfostrip="false">
        <head
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/head"/>
        <headlibs
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/headlibs"/>
        <header
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/header">
            <leftnavigation
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/leftnavigation"
                iconClass="iconClass2"/>
            <rightnavigation
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/rightnavigation"
                iconClass="iconClass2">
                <countrylistdropdown
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/countrylistdropdown"/>
                <languagedropdown
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/languagedropdown"/>
            </rightnavigation>
            <mainnav
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/mainnav"/>
            <infostrip
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/infostrip"/>
            <breadcrumb
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/breadcrumb"/>
        </header>
        <headerpage
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/headerpage"/>
        <releasetitle
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/releasetitle"/>
        <key
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/parsys">
            <releasekeymessages
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/releasekeymessages"/>
        </key>
        <releasedescription
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/releasedescription"/>
        <prshare
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/prshare"/>
        <footer
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/footer">
            <sitemap
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/sitemap"/>
            <followus
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/followus"/>
            <newsletterform
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/newsletterform"/>
        </footer>
        <footlibs
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/footlibs"/>
        <copyright
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/copyright"/>
        <content
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/parsys">
            <grid
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-08-25T17:57:22.285+02:00"
                jcr:createdBy="a101309"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-08-25T17:57:22.285+02:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="a101309"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/layout/grid">
                <column1 jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured">
                    <richtext
                        jcr:created="{Date}2017-08-25T17:57:52.970+02:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="a101309"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-08-29T14:44:54.177+02:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="a101309"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/content/richtext"
                        text="&lt;p>&lt;b>Survival in the Internet age - for retail not an easy task. The rapid proliferation of smartphones and tablets has changed consumer behavior. Consumers today decide for themselves where, when and what channel to use when they are researching, shopping or getting in touch with a brand. Worldline [EUR Next: WLN] the European leader in payment and transaction services, has developed tailored products and solutions to enable retailers to connect their physical stores to the retail world. At EuroCIS 2015 in Düsseldorf (February 24 to 26) interested parties can learn more at booth A39 in Hall 9, about how with the help of the &amp;quot;Worldline Promotion Wall&amp;quot;, the &amp;quot;Worldline cash register&amp;quot; and the application &amp;quot;Scan me Buy me&amp;quot; they can improve the shopping experience for their customers.&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Frankfurt/Main, 12. February 2015&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>With the rise of smartphone usage in Germany[i] and around the world, retailers now have to serve a connected consumer who will use all channels available (smart phone, tablets, physical shops) to look, decide and pay for shopping. For the retailer, this is both a blessing and a curse. With the smart phone, the retailer can reach the consumer directly. The challenge is how best to do this for the benefit of the retailer and the consumer.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;blockquote>&lt;span class=&quot;block--featured--title&quot;>Wolf Kunisch, Head of the Global Business Line Financial Processing &amp;amp; Software Licensing and CEO Germany &amp;amp; CEE at Worldline, says:&lt;/span> „In this new cross-channel world, it is the smartphone that can best bridge the physical digital worlds. For example, once the customer is in the shop, merchants can influence and increase sales by providing advice via their mobile sites. After all consumers want to touch the products, feel, try and in the ideal case take it home with them immediately. By integrating mobile trends such as mobile coupons, dealers can better persuade their customers to buy.&amp;quot;&lt;/blockquote>&#xa;&lt;p>To show how this can be achieved, Worldline presents at this year's EuroCIS a cross-channel solution. The Worldline Promotion Wall innovatively combines concepts of digital signage with digital couponing. Discount vouchers can be displayed on a large interactive digital screen and registered via an app via QR code. So retailers reach their customers at the right time through the right medium. In addition, the solution provides a campaign manager, which helps to plan, place and control individual discounts on the Promotion Wall. Customers can scan a coupon will then have a limited period of time to redeem the coupon in that store and benefit from the promotion.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>The company also presents Worldline Cash Register, a tablet-based solution to drive sales at the store through cross- and up-sell offers. The Worldline Cash Register today offers sellers in retail stores fast and easy access to the entire product catalogue. With this solution, retailers can also benefit from a consolidated view of their cross-channel activity with a back office providing reporting.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Thanks to augmented reality consumers can scan pictures with their smartphone and immediately get more access to further product information such as price, availability, colors, sizes and more. With Scan Me, Buy Me Worldline presents a solution that exactly uses this technology to allow customers an even more comfortable and above all personalized shopping experience. Since the user can be identified with this application, he has a real-time personalization to its respective preferences tailored information - this ensures relevant service in real time.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Worldline has more than 850,000 payment terminals installed in Europe, which ensure a fast and safe execution of transactions and thus fulfill the expectations of the customers. In addition, the versatile payment terminals are provided with the same customized single-chip system architecture. Costly downtime is thus limited to a minimum by safe download options for software updates and security Keys. Since May 2014 the contactless mobile payment terminal YOXIMO of Worldline is available on the German market and was awarded by the German Banking Committee as the fastest mobile device and received all necessary approvals.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Visit Worldline from 24 - 26 February 2014 at the EuroCIS in Düsseldorf and get in touch with the experts on electronic payment and transaction services at stand A39 in Hall 9 about the latest tools for a seamless customer experience. We can also arrange individual appointments in advance for you.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h3>About Worldline&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>Worldline [Euronext: WLN] is the European leader in the payments and transactional services industry. Worldline delivers new-generation services, enabling its customers to offer smooth and innovative solutions to the end consumer. Key actor for B2B2C industries, with 40 years of experience, Worldline supports and contributes to the success of all businesses and administrative services in a perpetually evolving market. Worldline offers a unique and flexible business model built around a global and growing portfolio, thus enabling end-to-end support. Worldline activities are organized around three axes: Merchant Services &amp;amp; Terminals, Mobility &amp;amp; e-Transactional Services, Financial Processing Services &amp;amp; Software Licensing. Worldline employs more than 7,200 people worldwide and generated 1.12 billion euros in revenues (pro forma) in 2013. Worldline is an Atos company. &lt;a title=&quot;www.worldline.com&quot; href=&quot;http://www.worldline.com&quot;>worldline.com.&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;i>[i] From 2013 to 2014, it has increased, according to a study by the Federal Association of the Digital Economy in cooperation with Google and TNS[i] by 25 percent.&lt;/i>&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                        textIsRich="true"/>
                </column1>
            </grid>
        </content>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
