<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:contextHubPath="/etc/cloudsettings/default/contexthub"
        cq:contextHubSegmentsPath="/etc/segmentation/contexthub"
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2017-10-09T15:13:19.198+02:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="a598986"
        cq:lastReplicated="{Date}2017-10-30T17:57:39.809+01:00"
        cq:lastReplicatedBy="a631192"
        cq:lastReplicationAction="Activate"
        cq:tags="[blog:epayment,blog:retail,blog:customer-experience,blog:digital-transformation]"
        cq:template="/apps/gotomarket/templates/blogarticle"
        jcr:description="Digital is transforming the customer journey and, more particularly, the payment, key step in this journey. We talked with Michel-Ange Camhi about this Digital Transformation of payments."
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-09-10T19:45:17.752+02:00"
        jcr:lastModifiedBy="a646217"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="The digital transformation of the customer journey and of payments"
        jcr:uuid="4f75f879-52b4-4a2f-9522-85c523d983f4"
        sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/pages/blogarticle"
        authorImage="/content/dam/worldline/images/blog/author/mac-80x80.png"
        authorName="Michel-Ange Camhi"
        authorText="Strategy and business development for mobile payments and our WL Wallet offer"
        categories="[category:solutions,category:business-insights]"
        categories_x0040_TypeHint="String[]"
        hideInNav="false"
        imagePath="/content/dam/worldline/images/blog/header/bg-nfc-hand.jpg"
        isExternalContactUsUrl="false"
        isExternalJoinUsUrl="false"
        isStickyContactHidden="false"
        noExtentionContactUs="false"
        noExtentionJoinUs="false"
        showbrand="false"
        showinfostrip="false"
        title="The digital transformation&#xd;&#xa;of the customer journey and of payments">
        <head
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/head"/>
        <headlibs
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/headlibs"/>
        <header
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/header">
            <leftnavigation
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/leftnavigation"
                iconClass="iconClass2"/>
            <rightnavigation
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/rightnavigation"
                iconClass="iconClass2">
                <countrylistdropdown
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/countrylistdropdown"/>
                <languagedropdown
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/languagedropdown"/>
            </rightnavigation>
            <mainnav
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/mainnav"/>
            <infostrip
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/infostrip"/>
            <breadcrumbblog
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/breadcrumbblog"/>
        </header>
        <headerblog
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/headerblog"/>
        <singleauthor
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/singleauthor"/>
        <prshare
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/prshare"/>
        <stayintouch
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/stayintouch"/>
        <footer
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/footer">
            <sitemap
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/sitemap"/>
            <followus
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/followus"/>
            <newsletterform
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/newsletterform"/>
        </footer>
        <footlibs
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/footlibs"/>
        <copyright
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/copyright"/>
        <content
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/parsys">
            <richtext
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-09-10T19:45:59.547+02:00"
                jcr:createdBy="a646217"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-09-10T19:50:20.378+02:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="a646217"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/content/richtext"
                text="&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h3>Digital is transforming the customer journey and, more particularly, the payment, key step in this journey. Can you tell us more about this?&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>Indeed, the digital transformation also influences payments. This payment needs to be both simple and secured in order to make the experience efficient and fluid.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h3>Concretely, how does the digital transformation change payments?&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>In order to illustrate this phenomenon, we can take a look at the Uber customer journey. In order to use this service, the customer downloads the mobile app, creates a secured account and registers his payment method on the app. Each time he uses this service, the customer receives the invoice via email and gets directly billed on his registered payment method, without any additional interactions.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>This kind of customer experience is positive but, because the payment occurs without the physical presence of the payment method or the use of 3DSecure*, merchants are then fully responsible in case of frauds. This also results in additional costs for merchants who need to put in place anti-fraud tools to protect themselves.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Our strategic vision to efficiently combine simplicity and security of mobile payments includes the three following elements:&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;ul>&#xa;&lt;li>&lt;span class=&quot;styled&quot;>The strong and secured registration of the consumer and his mobile by using 3DSecure, for example, at the time of the addition of the payment card in the application;&lt;/span>&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>&lt;span class=&quot;styled&quot;>The strong authentication of the consumer and his mobile at the time of the payment, through entering a PIN code or using fingerprints, for example;&lt;/span>&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>&lt;span class=&quot;styled&quot;>And a secured digital identity container, more commonly known as a Wallet, capable of handling multiple payment use cases for merchants as well as the lifecycle of the registered payment methods.&lt;/span>&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;/ul>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Combining these three vectors leads to a fluid payment experience for customers and to limited risks for merchants.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>The Worldline Wallet meets these three requirements and improves the conversion rate of online and in-store purchases without having to compromise on financial risk management and therefore reinforcing client engagement.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h3>How does the Worldline Wallet help merchants in regards to the digital transformation of their customer journey?&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>The Worldline Wallet allows for secured storage of key customer identity data, which permits merchants to not have to ask for them at each transaction. It also brings about a strong and transparent security, based on a software solution, which is already used by banks for their mobile authentication.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h3>In your opinion, what are tomorrow’s trends in the payment industry?&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>I think it is obvious that the mobile will be more and more used as a payment method in various forms. M-commerce is currently the fastest growing sector. Tomorrow, the mobile will accompany us through our in-store journey, before, during and after our purchases in physical retail.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h3>Thank you for your time today, Michel-Ange. I will leave you with one final question: if you could invent a new innovative solution to help with one of your daily tasks, in your professional and/or private life, what would it be and why?&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>I am hesitating between teleportation and cloning but, ideally, it would be a way to teleport with very little impact on our environment because, as we can see these days, the ramp-up of our transportation weighs heavily in terms of ecological footprint.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;i>* 3DSecure is a secured protocol for online payments.&lt;/i>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                textIsRich="true"/>
        </content>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
