<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:contextHubPath="/etc/cloudsettings/default/contexthub"
        cq:contextHubSegmentsPath="/etc/segmentation/contexthub"
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2017-11-27T18:17:17.074+01:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="fr20437"
        cq:lastReplicated="{Date}2017-11-27T18:27:23.632+01:00"
        cq:lastReplicatedBy="fr20437"
        cq:lastReplicationAction="Activate"
        cq:tags="[article:general]"
        cq:template="/apps/gotomarket/templates/releasearticle"
        jcr:description="Paris, 18 February 2015 - Worldline [Euronext: WLN], the European leader in the payments and transactional services industry, and its partner Awabot are offering an innovative POS communication tool to expand its range of multi-channel contact management solutions. The Contact solution from Worldline enables global and unified management of all inbound and outbound contacts on all channels used by the general public: voice, SMS, email, chat and social networks. And now, thanks to the Beam Pro telepresence robot, remote expert agents can “teleport” themselves in-store."
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-08-25T18:18:55.416+02:00"
        jcr:lastModifiedBy="a101309"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Worldline expands its Contact range of multi-channel solutions to include a telepresence robot "
        jcr:uuid="eca572f4-d03f-440d-bb89-087889c1b9bc"
        sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/pages/releasearticle"
        brand="worldline"
        categories_x0040_TypeHint="String[]"
        creationDate="{Date}2015-02-18T08:00:00.000+01:00"
        hideInNav="false"
        imagePath="/content/dam/gotomarket/uploads/bg-header-industries.jpg"
        keywords="Worldline, expands, Contact, range, multi-channel, solutions, telepresence, robot"
        onTime="{Date}2015-02-18T08:00:00.000+01:00"
        showbrand="false"
        showinfostrip="false">
        <head
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/head"/>
        <headlibs
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/headlibs"/>
        <header
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/header">
            <leftnavigation
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/leftnavigation"
                iconClass="iconClass2"/>
            <rightnavigation
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/rightnavigation"
                iconClass="iconClass2">
                <countrylistdropdown
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/countrylistdropdown"/>
                <languagedropdown
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/languagedropdown"/>
            </rightnavigation>
            <mainnav
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/mainnav"/>
            <infostrip
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/infostrip"/>
            <breadcrumb
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/breadcrumb"/>
        </header>
        <headerpage
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/headerpage"/>
        <releasetitle
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/releasetitle"/>
        <key
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/parsys">
            <releasekeymessages
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/releasekeymessages"/>
        </key>
        <releasedescription
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/releasedescription"/>
        <prshare
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/prshare"/>
        <footer
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/footer">
            <sitemap
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/sitemap"/>
            <followus
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/followus"/>
            <newsletterform
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/newsletterform"/>
        </footer>
        <footlibs
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/footlibs"/>
        <copyright
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/copyright"/>
        <content
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/parsys">
            <grid
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-08-25T18:11:32.001+02:00"
                jcr:createdBy="a101309"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-08-25T18:11:32.001+02:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="a101309"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/layout/grid">
                <column1 jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured">
                    <richtext
                        jcr:created="{Date}2017-08-25T18:11:49.975+02:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="a101309"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-08-29T14:44:30.935+02:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="a101309"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/content/richtext"
                        text="&lt;p>Paris, 18 February 2015&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Worldline [Euronext: WLN], the European leader in the payments and transactional services industry, and its partner Awabot are offering an innovative POS communication tool to expand its range of multi-channel contact management solutions. The Contact solution from Worldline enables global and unified management of all inbound and outbound contacts on all channels used by the general public: voice, SMS, email, chat and social networks. And now, thanks to the Beam Pro telepresence robot, remote expert agents can “teleport” themselves in-store.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>With “expert” agents and users connecting through a telepresence solution, specialists can provide all their expertise at the point of sale. A communicative and remotely controlled avatar robot translates into a brand-new video-conferencing experience. This innovative communication tool allows call centre agents to strengthen the arguments put forward by the salespeople working in-store, face-to-face with a new digital consumer, who could well be very knowledgeable, demanding, and will often have prepared their visit online before coming in-store. The “teleported” agent provides appropriate assistance to make it easier to conclude complex sales and to turn a perfectly ordinary customer experience into one that is truly unique! Combined with the multi-channel contact management solution from Worldline, the Awabot product strengthens the range of possible interactions with brand customers.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;blockquote>“The installed robot can be used to ‘teleport’ a specialist agent in-store from their call centre for the purpose of providing any information necessary to complete the purchase. Robotics combined with the remote call centre agent’s expertise will improve the conversion rate at the point of sale, thereby reducing showrooming. Worldline is working with its long-term partner Awabot to enhance the user experience which is so important to our customers,” &lt;span class=&quot;block--featured--title&quot;>explains Olivier Stuckens, Managing Director of Global Mobility &amp;amp; e-Transactional Services from Worldline.&lt;/span>&lt;/blockquote>&#xa;&lt;p>Beam Pro is a telepresence robot that allows people to be in two places at once. Combining a top-of-the-range audio and video system and freedom of movement, Beam Pro breaks down the barriers of traditional video-conferencing equipment, which are ill-suited to a point of sale. It’s extremely easy to use: all you need is a computer featuring a built-in webcam and an Internet connection and Beam Pro is turned into a remote avatar which allows users to interact with people, wherever they are in the world.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;blockquote>“Awabot is delighted that it has been able to help expand Worldline’s Contact offering with its innovation, which is guaranteed to offer an unrivalled customer experience. Beam Pro signals a new approach to video-conferencing by means of an exclusive, hands-on experience: not only does Beam Pro enable contact between individuals, it also gives them the opportunity to extend their range and to independently interact in the best way possible from any location,” &lt;span class=&quot;block--featured--title&quot;>affirms Bruno Bonnell, President of Awabot.&lt;/span>&lt;/blockquote>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Proven expertise in managing contact centres&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xa;Supplied exclusively in service mode by Worldline, Contact is a solution integrated in an end-to-end service offering – from collecting multichannel operators to connecting users with call-centre agents. Featuring complete web interfaces that interfere very little with the IP extension, it guarantees swift placement and has no impact on the infrastructure of call centres. Independent of any telephony range, its virtual ACD benefits enable contacts to be routed to several sites regardless of their number and geographical location, and to provide global administration and supervision services.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Worldline will be at the next Call Centre World trade fair (CCW 15) in Berlin&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xa;Worldline will be showcasing its Contact offering and the Beam Pro robot both at its booth and during a conference at Europe’s biggest event dedicated to call centres and the customer service industry. The trade fair will take place in Berlin from 24 to 26 February 2015.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h3>About Worldline&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>Worldline [Euronext:WLN] is the European leader in the payments and transactional services industry. Worldline delivers new-generation services, enabling its customers to offer smooth and innovative solutions to the end consumer. Key actor for B2B2C industries, with 40 years of experience, Worldline supports and contributes to the success of all businesses and administrative services in a perpetually evolving market. Worldline offers a unique and flexible business model built around a global and growing portfolio, thus enabling end-to-end support. Worldline activities are organised around three axes: Merchant Services &amp;amp; Terminals, Mobility &amp;amp; e-Transactional Services, Financial Processing Services &amp;amp; Software Licensing. Worldline employs more than 7,200 people worldwide and generated 1.12 billion euros revenues (pro forma) in 2013. Worldline is an Atos company. &lt;a title=&quot;www.worldline.com&quot; href=&quot;http://www.worldline.com&quot;>www.worldline.com&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h3>For more information, contact:&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>Caroline Crouch&lt;br>&#xa;Tel: +44 77 33 310086&lt;br>&#xa;Email: &lt;a title=&quot;caroline.crouch@atos.net&quot; href=&quot;mailto:caroline.crouch@atos.net&quot;>caroline.crouch@atos.net&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                        textIsRich="true"/>
                </column1>
            </grid>
        </content>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
