<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:contextHubPath="/etc/cloudsettings/default/contexthub"
        cq:contextHubSegmentsPath="/etc/segmentation/contexthub"
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2017-11-09T17:04:58.697+01:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="a480019"
        cq:lastReplicated="{Date}2017-11-01T14:37:37.992+01:00"
        cq:lastReplicatedBy="a480019"
        cq:lastReplicationAction="Activate"
        cq:template="/apps/gotomarket/templates/content"
        jcr:description="Use of equensWorldline’s website and connected websites belonging to businesses under the direct or indirect supervision of equensWorldline is subject to the following conditions and restrictions."
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-11-01T14:36:17.770+01:00"
        jcr:lastModifiedBy="a480019"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Disclaimer"
        jcr:uuid="e5eff66e-47c8-4a48-a81b-8b98725f9f40"
        sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/pages/content"
        browserTabTitle="Disclaimer | equensWorldline"
        carouselItems="\{&quot;imagePath&quot;:&quot;/content/dam/gotomarket/bg-header-solutions.jpg&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;&quot;,&quot;subtitle&quot;:&quot;&quot;,&quot;description&quot;:&quot;&quot;,&quot;link&quot;:&quot;&quot;}"
        creationDate="{Date}2017-10-04T14:50:00.000+02:00"
        hideInNav="false"
        imagePath="/content/dam/equensworldline/images/articles/ew_article_088.jpg"
        showbrand="false"
        showinfostrip="false">
        <head
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/head"/>
        <headlibs
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/headlibs"/>
        <header
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/header">
            <leftnavigation
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/leftnavigation"
                iconClass="iconClass2"/>
            <rightnavigation
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/rightnavigation"
                iconClass="iconClass2">
                <countrylistdropdown
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/countrylistdropdown"/>
                <languagedropdown
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/languagedropdown"/>
            </rightnavigation>
            <mainnav
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/mainnav"/>
            <infostrip
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/infostrip"/>
            <content
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/parsys">
                <search
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/search"/>
            </content>
            <breadcrumb
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/breadcrumb"/>
        </header>
        <headerpage
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/headerpage"/>
        <contactus
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/contactus"/>
        <footer
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/footer">
            <sitemap
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/sitemap"/>
            <followus
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/followus"/>
            <newsletterform
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/newsletterform"/>
        </footer>
        <footlibs
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/footlibs"/>
        <copyright
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/copyright"/>
        <content
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/parsys">
            <section
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-10-03T15:53:31.395+02:00"
                jcr:createdBy="a480019"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-10-03T15:53:31.395+02:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="a480019"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/layout/section">
                <items
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/parsys">
                    <grid
                        jcr:created="{Date}2017-10-03T15:53:39.232+02:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="a480019"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-10-03T15:53:39.232+02:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="a480019"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/layout/grid">
                        <column1
                            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/parsys">
                            <titleh2
                                jcr:created="{Date}2017-10-03T15:53:53.026+02:00"
                                jcr:createdBy="a480019"
                                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-10-03T15:54:08.015+02:00"
                                jcr:lastModifiedBy="a480019"
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/content/titleH2"
                                showDots="false"
                                title="Disclaimer"
                                titleAlignment="left"/>
                            <richtext
                                jcr:created="{Date}2017-10-03T15:54:18.741+02:00"
                                jcr:createdBy="a480019"
                                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-10-25T15:10:47.827+02:00"
                                jcr:lastModifiedBy="a480019"
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/content/richtext"
                                text="&lt;p>Use of equensWorldline’s website and connected websites belonging to businesses under the direct or indirect supervision of equensWorldline (hereinafter collectively referred to as ‘associated businesses’) is subject to the following conditions and restrictions.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Access to and use of these websites (hereinafter collectively referred to as ‘the websites’) implies that the user agrees with the following:&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>equensWorldline does not accept liability for any damage resulting from access to and use of the websites, nor does equensWorldline offer any guarantee ensuring error-free and continuous operation of the websites.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>equensWorldline does not offer any guarantee, whether implicit or explicit, regarding the reasonableness, accuracy or completeness of the information published on the websites, or any websites to which access is offered via the websites. The associated businesses, as well as the directors and personnel of the associated businesses, accept no form of liability for the information and/or recommendations published on the websites, or on websites to which the websites offer access. Such information and recommendations are subject to change without any obligation of prior notification. Furthermore, the information may not be relied upon and cannot and may not be used as advice in any form whatsoever.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>References or hyperlinks to other websites not belonging to one of the associated businesses are solely included on the websites as information for users. The associated businesses do not offer any guarantee or accept any type of liability with regard to the content of such websites.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Privacy statement&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xa;equensWorldline undertakes all possible precautions to protect the privacy of its customers, suppliers and employees. This also applies to all visitors to this website. Any information provided through this website is treated confidentially and with the same level of security we apply to our transaction services. However, because of the insecure nature of the internet, equensWorldline cannot accept any liability for the loss or misuse of submitted data while it is in transmission.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Use and sharing of information&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xa;By submitting information through this website, you consent to the use of your personal data. This means that any information you may provide through the equensWorldline website is received by us with your consent.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>The information received though this website may be used for market research and the provision of other services by equensWorldline, its associated businesses and other third parties.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Use of e-mail addresses&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xa;If equensWorldline receives your e-mail address this address will not be used to send you any other kind of marketing information or information about services provided by equensWorldline or its associated businesses unless you do explicitly state that you wish to receive information.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Log files&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xa;equensWorldline uses IP addresses to analyse trends, manage the website, track users’ movements and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information, and the analysis of addresses is only used to assist equensWorldline in providing an effective service on this website.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Use of cookies&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xa;equensWorldline uses cookies to store basic information that helps us establish whether you have visited the website before. However, if you visit the website from a different computer to the one you registered on, we will not be able to find the cookie. We&amp;nbsp;use cookies for the following objectives: 1) to assist users of our website, 2) to examine how we can make the website even more user-friendly, and 3) for research and analyses. We do not use re-targeting cookies (which are used to track users after they have visited a website, and display advertisements for other similar websites). If you do not want a cookie to be created on your computer, use the appropriate function of your web browser to disable the creation of cookies.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Copyright&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xa;All information visible on the website, including text, photographs, illustrations, graphic material, business or other names, logos and brand names of goods and services, fall under the ownership or licence of the associated businesses, and are protected by copyright, trademark law, and/or any other intellectual property rights law. The (intellectual) property rights are in no way transferable to parties, legal or otherwise, who have access to the website. The content of the website may be used exclusively for non-commercial, private purposes. Users of the website are prohibited from reproducing, altering, removing, sending, distributing, spreading or making available for profit any of the websites contents to third parties (for instance, after you have contacted equensWorldline by e-mail, if you have used any part of this website to inform us that you wish to receive information, or if you have downloaded information), without the express written permission of equensWorldline or its associated businesses.&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                                textIsRich="true"/>
                        </column1>
                    </grid>
                </items>
            </section>
        </content>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
