<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:contextHubPath="/etc/cloudsettings/default/contexthub"
        cq:contextHubSegmentsPath="/etc/segmentation/contexthub"
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2017-11-27T18:12:06.762+01:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="fr20437"
        cq:lastReplicated="{Date}2017-11-27T18:13:17.860+01:00"
        cq:lastReplicatedBy="fr20437"
        cq:lastReplicationAction="Activate"
        cq:tags="[article:]"
        cq:template="/apps/gotomarket/templates/releasearticle"
        jcr:description="Bezons, 16 march 2016 – Worldline [Euronext : WLN], European market leader in payments and transactional services, wins three 2016 PayForum Awards for its WL eBanking Payment Services solution’s “Mandate &amp; SEPA transaction” service, its WL Connected Piggy Bank innovative concept and its WL Trusted Authentication with FIDO compliance solution.&#xd;&#xa;"
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-11-27T18:12:06.758+01:00"
        jcr:lastModifiedBy="fr20437"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Worldline wins three 2016 PayForum Awards rewarding its innovation capability in payment and digital services"
        jcr:uuid="16fc7ac3-c5f2-4748-847f-bdc29547ad76"
        sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/pages/releasearticle"
        brand="worldline"
        categories="[article:]"
        categories_x0040_TypeHint="String[]"
        creationDate="{Date}2016-03-16T18:11:00.000+01:00"
        hideInNav="false"
        imagePath="/content/dam/gotomarket/uploads/bg-header-industries.jpg"
        isExternalContactUsUrl="false"
        isExternalJoinUsUrl="false"
        isStickyContactHidden="false"
        keywords="Worldline, 2016 PayForum Awards rewarding, payment and digital services"
        noExtentionContactUs="false"
        noExtentionJoinUs="false"
        showbrand="false"
        showinfostrip="false">
        <head
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/head"/>
        <headlibs
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/headlibs"/>
        <header
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/header">
            <leftnavigation
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/leftnavigation"
                iconClass="iconClass2"/>
            <rightnavigation
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/rightnavigation"
                iconClass="iconClass2">
                <countrylistdropdown
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/countrylistdropdown"/>
                <languagedropdown
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/languagedropdown"/>
            </rightnavigation>
            <mainnav
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/mainnav"/>
            <infostrip
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/infostrip"/>
            <breadcrumb
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/breadcrumb"/>
        </header>
        <headerpage
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/headerpage"/>
        <releasetitle
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/releasetitle"/>
        <key
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/parsys">
            <releasekeymessages
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/releasekeymessages"/>
        </key>
        <releasedescription
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/releasedescription"/>
        <prshare
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/prshare"/>
        <footer
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/footer">
            <sitemap
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/sitemap"/>
            <followus
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/followus"/>
            <newsletterform
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/newsletterform"/>
        </footer>
        <footlibs
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/footlibs"/>
        <copyright
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/copyright"/>
        <content
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/parsys">
            <grid
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-08-28T11:05:06.347+02:00"
                jcr:createdBy="a646217"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-08-28T11:05:06.347+02:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="a646217"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/layout/grid">
                <column1
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/parsys">
                    <richtext
                        jcr:created="{Date}2017-08-28T11:05:13.150+02:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="a646217"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-08-28T11:06:56.535+02:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="a646217"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/content/richtext"
                        text="&lt;p>&lt;b>Bezons, 16 march 2016 – Worldline [Euronext&amp;nbsp;: WLN], European market leader in payments and transactional services, wins three 2016 PayForum Awards for its WL eBanking Payment Services solution’s “Mandate &amp;amp; SEPA transaction” service, its WL Connected Piggy Bank innovative concept and its WL Trusted Authentication with FIDO compliance solution.&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Mandate &amp;amp; SEPA transaction services: the secured digital recurring payment&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Worldline is engaged in non-card payments since 2006 through its WL eBanking Payment Services solution. With the 2014 SEPA migration, the solution became European and was enriched with the addition of the direct debit payment method, named “Mandate &amp;amp; SEPA transaction services”, which is composed of 4 modules:&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;ul>&#xa;&lt;li>SEPA mandates and transactions management : SEPA mandate creation and the conversion of domestic formats to SEPA formats, production of payment instructions in SEPA format (direct debit and credit transfer),&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>E-signature of SEPA mandates,&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>Fraud: fraud management tools in simple or scoring modes,&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>PayButton: payment platform for the development of recurring payments in e-commerce.&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;/ul>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>This service, which is actually used by more than 700 creditors all over Europe, allows merchants and consumers to find the right balance between security and digitalization of the recurring payment thanks to the electronic signature of mandate.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>For more information, &lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;http://worldline.com/content/dam/worldline/documents/publications/brochures/offre-ebanking-4p-en-ld.pdf&quot;>brochure eBanking Payment Services&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>WL Connected Piggy Bank&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Thanks to IoT, Worldline offers WL Connected Piggy Bank, a personified banking service through a connected piggy bank. It has a complete ecosystem combining a smart object, an online platform and a mobile banking application. This innovative concept encourages simple and fun social interactions between children, their families and the piggy bank.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>The piggy bank becomes an easy-to-use smart bank savings enabler, always available, whether it is in the kids’ room or in the cloud through the mobile application and online banking. This solution’s scalability allows it to be enriched with new services such as the management of the banking mobility and reliability of banking information in real time.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>For more information, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WzJMmALz864&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>video WL Connected Piggy Bank&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>WL Trusted Authentication with FIDO (Fast ID Online) compliance&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Worldline offers a solution designed and developed to address its clients’ needs for end users’ strong authentication during the access to an online personal space or during the approval of a financial transaction, while maintaining an efficient user experience.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Simple and economical, the solution is based on the well-established concept of &amp;quot;what I own” (the mobile), &amp;quot;what I know&amp;quot; (a secret code) or of &amp;quot;what I am&amp;quot; (the fingerprint). The combination of, at least, two of these factors, is considered as a strong authentication, according to the FIDO alliance. Biometrics having been adopted by the main smartphones manufacturers (Apple and Samsung) as a security and identification component, our offer WL Trusted Authentication with FIDO compliance is ready to be used on the latest smartphones generation as well as future ones.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>It also offers an additional physically owned factor (a FIDO key) which strengthens the authentication process and can be used on the customer’s different devices of via USB, NFC or BLE (Bluetooth Low Energy).&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>FIDO (Fast ID Online) is a renowned technical specification, based on an open and interoperable set of mechanisms, for online strong authentication. It is currently supported by more than 200 large IT companies. The coupling of our strong authentication with FIDO interoperability opens up new business opportunities for our customers but also prepares them in terms of compliancy with upcoming regulations.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>For more information about our WL Trusted Authentication solution, &lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VSmNVtdRwQ0&quot;>video&lt;/a> or &lt;a target=&quot;_blank&quot; href=&quot;http://worldline.com/content/dam/worldline/documents/publications/brochures/offre-trusted-authentication-4p-en-ld.pdf&quot;>brochure&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;blockquote>&lt;span class=&quot;block--featured--title&quot;>Marc-Henri Desportes, Worldline’s General Manager declares: &lt;/span>“&lt;i>Our solutions are fully aligned with Worldline’s innovation strategy and answer to an ever changing environment which requires more security, interoperability and innovative services for end users. Worldline continuously invests in solutions to support banks and merchants in the long term by bringing them new competitive advantages to face the many challenges and opportunities resulting from digital transformation.&lt;/i>”&lt;/blockquote>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Each year, the PayForum Awards reward the most innovative solutions and products of the payment industry in France.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>In 2016, applicants submitted 147 applications and only 16 winners were chosen by the jury.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Contact Presse Worldline&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Cendrella Bourjaili&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Email &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:fabien.aufrechter@havasww.com&quot;>cendrella.bourjaili@worldline.com&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>About Worldline&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Worldline [Euronext: WLN] is the European leader in the payments and transactional services industry. Worldline delivers new-generation services, enabling its customers to offer smooth and innovative solutions to the end consumer. Key actor for B2B2C industries, with 40 years of experience, Worldline supports and contributes to the success of all businesses and administrative services in a perpetually evolving market. Worldline offers a unique and flexible business model built around a global and growing portfolio, thus enabling end-to-end support. Worldline activities are organized around three axes: Merchant Services &amp;amp; Terminals, Mobility &amp;amp; e-Transactional Services, Financial Processing Services &amp;amp; Software Licensing. Worldline employs more than 7,300 people worldwide and generated 1.22 billion euros revenues in 2015. Worldline is an Atos company. worldline.com&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Twitter: &lt;/b>#Worldline wins three 2016 #PayForum Awards rewarding its #innovation capability in #payment and #digital services.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Facebook: &lt;/b>#Worldline wins three 2016 #PayForum Awards rewarding its #innovation capability in #payment and #digital services.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>LinkedindIn: &lt;/b>Worldline wins three 2016 PayForum Awards rewarding its innovation capability in payment and digital services.&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                        textIsRich="true"/>
                </column1>
            </grid>
        </content>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
