<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:contextHubPath="/etc/cloudsettings/default/contexthub"
        cq:contextHubSegmentsPath="/etc/segmentation/contexthub"
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2017-11-27T18:18:59.709+01:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="fr20437"
        cq:lastReplicated="{Date}2017-11-27T18:28:22.090+01:00"
        cq:lastReplicatedBy="fr20437"
        cq:lastReplicationAction="Activate"
        cq:tags="[article:business,article:general]"
        cq:template="/apps/gotomarket/templates/releasearticle"
        jcr:description="Berlin, 4 September 2014 – Worldline, [WLN], the European leader and a global player in the payments and transactional services industry, today announced that it is joining theEEBus Initiative e.V, the broadest platform worldwide in terms of the definition of new content for Internet of Things (IoT) and  Cloud services."
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-08-29T17:36:08.777+02:00"
        jcr:lastModifiedBy="a101309"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Worldline joins EEBus to extend its connected home solutions"
        jcr:uuid="8528aa4d-0106-40f5-a62a-8048cd958bf4"
        sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/pages/releasearticle"
        brand="worldline"
        categories_x0040_TypeHint="String[]"
        creationDate="{Date}2014-09-04T10:00:00.000+02:00"
        hideInNav="false"
        imagePath="/content/dam/gotomarket/uploads/bg-header-industries.jpg"
        keywords="worldline, eebus, connected home solutions"
        showbrand="false"
        showinfostrip="false">
        <head
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/head"/>
        <headlibs
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/headlibs"/>
        <header
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/header">
            <leftnavigation
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/leftnavigation"
                iconClass="iconClass2"/>
            <rightnavigation
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/rightnavigation"
                iconClass="iconClass2">
                <countrylistdropdown
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/countrylistdropdown"/>
                <languagedropdown
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/languagedropdown"/>
            </rightnavigation>
            <mainnav
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/mainnav"/>
            <infostrip
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/infostrip"/>
            <breadcrumb
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/breadcrumb"/>
        </header>
        <headerpage
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/headerpage"/>
        <releasetitle
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/releasetitle"/>
        <key
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/parsys">
            <releasekeymessages
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/releasekeymessages"/>
        </key>
        <releasedescription
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/releasedescription"/>
        <prshare
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/prshare"/>
        <footer
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/footer">
            <sitemap
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/sitemap"/>
            <followus
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/followus"/>
            <newsletterform
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/newsletterform"/>
        </footer>
        <footlibs
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/footlibs"/>
        <copyright
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/copyright"/>
        <content
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/parsys">
            <grid
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-08-29T17:29:20.506+02:00"
                jcr:createdBy="a101309"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-08-29T17:29:20.506+02:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="a101309"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/layout/grid">
                <column1 jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured">
                    <richtext
                        jcr:created="{Date}2017-08-29T17:29:35.293+02:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="a101309"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-08-29T17:35:39.190+02:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="a101309"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/content/richtext"
                        text="&lt;p>&lt;b>Berlin, 4 September 2014 – Worldline, [WLN], the European leader and a global player in the payments and transactional services industry, today announced that it is joining theEEBus Initiative e.V, the broadest platform worldwide in terms of the definition of new content for Internet of Things (IoT) and&amp;nbsp; Cloud services.&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Demand for connected home solutions is growing*. By working with EEBus Initiative e.V, Worldline can deliver the next generation of connected home solutions that can communicate with different branded devices, security and smart energy solutions. This means the user can easily control and monitor all devices in their home using a single command, for example to switch on or off all devices. With the connection to the smart energy solution, the user can also ask the washing machine to start when the electricity rate is cheapest or when their own solar panel will be producing energy. This is not only convenient but can also reduce costs and is more sustainable.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>The EEBus initiative is very active and includes representatives from those involved in&amp;nbsp; smart Energy and connected home. Its key differentiator is linking the different areas of smart energy, security and household devices. For example, through EEBus it is possible for a programme to be set to alert the user if the security system is on, so nobody is at home, at the same time as the oven. The user can then remotely switch off the oven if necessary.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Worldline brings its Cloud, Big Data &amp;amp; Security knowledge through its connected living offer and its Connected Living Enabler platform for Internet of Things. Security &amp;amp; Privacy are key in the home environment and Worldline holds a vast expertise in this field to ensure consumers can be confident their home and information about their home remains secure.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;blockquote>&lt;span class=&quot;block--featured--title&quot;>Olivier Stuckens, Managing Director Mobility &amp;amp; e-Transactional Services at at Worldline says:&lt;/span> “Worldline intends to be the enabler for Multi-Service-Operators (MSO) to offer and monetize services and apps for the home from different service vendors. The EEBus initiative is the most mature alliance we have found active in the standardization process of connected Home and has an original approach. It is not simply yet another protocol in the home. Moreover it provides ways to interconnect to most well established protocols such as ZigBee, KNX, EnOcean. We believe EEBus will soon become an important Connected Home standard and we are happy to become their international member.&lt;/blockquote>&#xa;&lt;blockquote>&lt;span class=&quot;block--featured--title&quot;>Peter Kellendonk, President at EEBus:&lt;/span> “We are delighted to welcome an international player such as Worldline as a member of our initiative. They have a long track record in developing innovative solutions and are very customer-oriented. The fact that they build cloud into their propositions is very appealing to us, and we look forward to developing a joint solution with them in the near future”.&lt;/blockquote>&#xa;&lt;p>* &lt;i>Frost &amp;amp; Sullivan predict 31% growth in Connected Living with $ 226 Billion in 2020 (June 2013, page 13)&lt;/i>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Discover Worldline at IFA Hall 11.1 Booth #20 or visit our virtual booth &lt;a title=&quot; http://fairs.worldline.com/ifa&quot; href=&quot; http://fairs.worldline.com/ifa&quot;>http://fairs.worldline.com/ifa&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h3>About Worldline&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>Worldline [Euronext:WLN] is the European leader and a global player in the payments and transactional services industry. Worldline delivers new-generation services, enabling its customers to offer smooth and innovative solutions to the end consumer. Key actor for B2B2C industries, with 40 years of experience, Worldline supports and contributes to the success of all businesses and administrative services in a perpetually evolving market. Worldline offers a unique and flexible business model built around a global and growing portfolio, thus enabling end-to-end support. Worldline activities are organised around three axes: Merchant Services &amp;amp; Terminals, Mobility &amp;amp; e-Transactional Services, Financial Processing Services &amp;amp; Software Licensing. Worldline employs more than 7,200 people worldwide and generated 1.12 billion euros revenues (pro forma) in 2013. Worldline is an Atos company. &lt;a title=&quot; www.worldline.com&quot; href=&quot;http:// www.worldline.com&quot;>www.worldline.com&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h3>About the EEBus Initiative e.V.&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>The non-profit organization EEBus Initiative e.V. networks the leading companies, associations and stakeholders in the German and international energy, telecommunications and electrical industry. Together, we develop EEBus as an open, standardised and consensus-oriented networking concept. Starting with linking Smart Grid and Smart Consumers, we are developing an approach above and beyond Smart Home and Building, to make a holistic concept for almost all Smart Devices. Through our combined strengths and competence we open up a new interdisciplinary market for smart connectivity. The aim: an increase in energy efficiency, comfort and security for the benefit of consumers, society, the environment and economy. Through active participation in the standardisation bodies, we are contributing to a modern, sustainable communication infrastructure and promoting networking and interoperability. www.eebus.org&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>For more information, please contact:&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Worldline&lt;br>&#xa;Caroline Crouch&lt;br>&#xa;+44 77 33 310086&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;a title=&quot;caroline.crouch@atos.net&quot; href=&quot;mailto:caroline.crouch@atos.net&quot;>caroline.crouch@atos.net&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>EEBus&lt;br>&#xa;Til Landwehrmann&lt;br>&#xa;+49 221 47 44 12 22;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br>&#xa;+49 151 – 57132306&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;a title=&quot;landwehrmann@eebus.org&quot; href=&quot;mailto:landwehrmann@eebus.org&quot;>landwehrmann@eebus.org&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                        textIsRich="true"/>
                </column1>
            </grid>
        </content>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
