<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:contextHubPath="/etc/cloudsettings/default/contexthub"
        cq:contextHubSegmentsPath="/etc/segmentation/contexthub"
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2017-11-27T17:44:04.555+01:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="fr20437"
        cq:lastReplicated="{Date}2017-11-29T17:32:46.858+01:00"
        cq:lastReplicatedBy="fr20437"
        cq:lastReplicationAction="Activate"
        cq:tags="[article:general,article:]"
        cq:template="/apps/gotomarket/templates/releasearticle"
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-11-27T17:44:04.551+01:00"
        jcr:lastModifiedBy="fr20437"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Worldline integrates Lyf Pay in its online payment solution WL Sips"
        jcr:uuid="d9532756-5f7c-46df-8b6a-0c3771051965"
        sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/pages/releasearticle"
        categories="[article:general,article:]"
        categories_x0040_TypeHint="String[]"
        creationDate="{Date}2017-09-29T17:43:00.000+02:00"
        hideInNav="false"
        imagePath="/content/dam/gotomarket/uploads/bg-header-industries.jpg"
        isExternalContactUsUrl="false"
        isExternalJoinUsUrl="false"
        isStickyContactHidden="false"
        keywords="worldline"
        noExtentionContactUs="false"
        noExtentionJoinUs="false"
        showbrand="false"
        showinfostrip="false">
        <head
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/head"/>
        <headlibs
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/headlibs"/>
        <header
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/header">
            <leftnavigation
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/leftnavigation"
                iconClass="iconClass2"/>
            <rightnavigation
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/rightnavigation"
                iconClass="iconClass2">
                <countrylistdropdown
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/countrylistdropdown"/>
                <languagedropdown
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/languagedropdown"/>
            </rightnavigation>
            <mainnav
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/mainnav"/>
            <infostrip
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/infostrip"/>
            <breadcrumb
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/breadcrumb"/>
        </header>
        <headerpage
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/headerpage"/>
        <releasetitle
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/releasetitle"/>
        <key
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/parsys">
            <releasekeymessages
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/releasekeymessages"/>
        </key>
        <releasedescription
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/releasedescription"/>
        <prshare
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/prshare"/>
        <footer
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/footer">
            <sitemap
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/sitemap"/>
            <followus
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/followus"/>
            <newsletterform
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/newsletterform"/>
        </footer>
        <footlibs
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/footlibs"/>
        <copyright
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/copyright"/>
        <content
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/parsys">
            <grid
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-09-27T15:22:00.305+02:00"
                jcr:createdBy="a646217"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-09-27T15:22:00.305+02:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="a646217"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/layout/grid">
                <column1
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/parsys">
                    <richtext
                        jcr:created="{Date}2017-09-27T15:22:10.296+02:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="a646217"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-09-27T19:23:28.021+02:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="fr20437"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/content/richtext"
                        text="&lt;p>&lt;b>Bezons – 29 September 2017: Worldline [Euronext: WLN], the European leader and a global player in the payments and transactional services industry, is now making the Lyf Pay wallet available to its merchants. Since 18 May 2017, Lyf Pay has been offering an innovative and secured multi-service mobile payment application for customer relationship management.&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Lyf Pay is the result of the merger between two French mobile payments initiatives: Fivory, which brings together Crédit Mutuel, Mastercard, Total, Oney and Auchan, and the Wa! application provided by Carrefour and BNP&amp;nbsp;Paribas. Lyf Pay is an application that centralises all of the customers' payment cards, coupons and loyalty points, and it can be customised by any merchant that adopts it.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>The scope of the application is extensive, covering in-store payments (from small local shops to large retail chains), online shopping, friends and family payments, and even charitable donations. By integrating payment cards, loyalty cards and coupons, Lyf Pay provides a unique and innovative solution to simplify its customers' lives and create a special relationship between consumers, merchants and banking partners.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;blockquote>&lt;b>Vincent Roland, Head of Merchant Services at Worldline,&lt;/b> said: &amp;quot;Worldline is very proud to add the Lyf Pay wallet to its range of payment options. By integrating this new mobile payment method, merchants will be able to give their consumers a better customer experience.&amp;quot;&lt;/blockquote>&#xa;&lt;blockquote>&lt;b>Christophe Dolique, CEO of Lyf Pay,&lt;/b> added: &amp;quot;We are delighted by this collaboration with Worldline, which really opens the door into the e-commerce sector for us.&amp;nbsp;The integration of Lyf Pay into the WL Sips online payment solution enables us to support our customers, particularly those in large-scale retail, across all the channels in which they are present.&amp;quot;&lt;/blockquote>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>About Worldline&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Worldline [Euronext: WLN] is the European leader and a global player in the payments and transactional services industry. Worldline delivers new-generation services, enabling its customers to offer smooth and innovative solutions to the end consumer. A key actor in the B2B2C sector, with nearly 45 years of experience, Worldline supports and contributes to the success of all businesses and administrative services in a perpetually evolving market. Worldline offers a unique and flexible business model built around a global and growing portfolio, thus enabling end-to-end support. Worldline activities are organized around three axes: Merchant Services, Mobility &amp;amp; eTransactional Services, and Financial Services including equensWorldline. Worldline has more than 8,700 employees around the world and generates an estimated pro forma turnover of around 1.5&amp;nbsp;billion euros a year. Worldline is an Atos company.&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;http://worldline.com/&quot; title=&quot;http://worldline.com/&quot;>worldline.com&lt;/a>&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>About Lyf Pay&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Lyf aims to offer both merchants and consumers an innovative, open and large-scale payment solution for customer relationship management. The result of the merger of Fivory and Wa!, two proven mobile payment solutions, Lyf responds to the major challenges faced by stakeholders in the payments industry and in commerce, which include developing new shopping experiences, managing customer relationships and monitoring the data gathered.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>As users become increasingly mobile and connected, Lyf aims to anchor mobile payment in a sustainable manner, and places great importance on partnership with merchants and consumers. In this context, Lyf has created the mobile payment solution Lyf Pay, an application that brings together all of the features users need to make their everyday lives easier, both in shops and online.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Incorporating mobile payments, loyalty cards, coupons and online offers, as well as friends and family payments and charitable donations, Lyf Pay is a complete application that is accessible to everyone and looks set to become a major ally for consumers in their day-to-day life.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>With the active support of leading players in their industry, many independent merchants and partners, particularly in the field of events (cultural, sport, etc.), and associations (cultural, sport, charitable, student, etc.), as well as in direct sales, Lyf Pay is a proven solution and is already operational.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Welcome to the world of Lyf Pay, the application that embodies payment today!&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Worldline press contact&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Teamfluence&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Tiphaine Hecketsweiler&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:th@teamfluence.eu&quot;>th@teamfluence.eu&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>+33 6 89 87 62 18&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                        textIsRich="true"/>
                </column1>
            </grid>
        </content>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
