<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:contextHubPath="/etc/cloudsettings/default/contexthub"
        cq:contextHubSegmentsPath="/etc/segmentation/contexthub"
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2017-11-20T18:46:28.716+01:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="fr20437"
        cq:template="/apps/gotomarket/templates/releasearticle"
        jcr:description="London, July 6th, 2017 – Worldline [Euronext: WLN], European leader in the payment and transactional services industry, has inked a deal with the UK’s largest rail franchise, Govia Thameslink Railway, to replace the operator’s current desktop Ticketing Issuing Services (TIS) with the Worldline Mobile Ticketing Service, @Station."
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-08-23T14:30:14.239+02:00"
        jcr:lastModifiedBy="a646217"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Title of the Press Release in French"
        jcr:uuid="181283d7-d4ba-4a0a-a168-fb3ae4da0fe6"
        sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/pages/releasearticle"
        brand="worldline"
        categories_x0040_TypeHint="String[]"
        hideInNav="false"
        imagePath="/content/dam/gotomarket/uploads/bg-header-industries.jpg"
        keywords="worldline, mobile ticketing, Govia Thameslink Railway"
        showbrand="false"
        showinfostrip="false">
        <head
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/head"/>
        <headlibs
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/headlibs"/>
        <header
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/header">
            <leftnavigation
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/leftnavigation"
                iconClass="iconClass2"/>
            <rightnavigation
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/rightnavigation"
                iconClass="iconClass2">
                <countrylistdropdown
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/countrylistdropdown"/>
                <languagedropdown
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/languagedropdown"/>
            </rightnavigation>
            <mainnav
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/mainnav"/>
            <infostrip
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/infostrip"/>
            <breadcrumb
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/breadcrumb"/>
        </header>
        <headerpage
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/headerpage"/>
        <releasetitle
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/releasetitle"/>
        <key
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/parsys">
            <releasekeymessages
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/releasekeymessages"/>
        </key>
        <releasedescription
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/releasedescription"/>
        <prshare
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/prshare"/>
        <footer
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/footer">
            <sitemap
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/sitemap"/>
            <followus
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/followus"/>
            <newsletterform
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/newsletterform"/>
        </footer>
        <footlibs
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/footlibs"/>
        <copyright
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/copyright"/>
        <content
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/parsys">
            <grid
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-08-23T14:24:03.539+02:00"
                jcr:createdBy="a646217"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-08-23T14:24:03.539+02:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="a646217"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/layout/grid">
                <column1
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/parsys">
                    <richtext
                        jcr:created="{Date}2017-08-23T14:24:28.203+02:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="a646217"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-08-23T14:29:01.026+02:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="a646217"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/content/richtext"
                        text="&lt;p>&lt;b>&lt;i>New mobile ticket system signals richer functionality and cost savings for UK’s largest rail franchise&lt;/i>&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>London, July 6th, 2017 – Worldline [Euronext: WLN], European leader in the payment and transactional services industry, has inked a deal with the UK’s largest rail franchise, Govia Thameslink Railway, to replace the operator’s current desktop Ticketing Issuing Services (TIS) with the Worldline Mobile Ticketing Service, @Station.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>The @Station system will provide significant advantages of a Mobile point-of-sale system, including the ability to ‘queue bust’ as well as cross and upsell both Rail Settlement Plan and non-RSP products to customers. It will also ensure that GTR is Direct Acquiring (DA) compliant.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>The upgraded systems are bolstering the technological capabilities across the GTR network at a time of modernisation for the UK’s busiest rail operator. The organisation is halfway through a transformation plan set to enhance the rail experience for passengers, while continuing to operate its growing interconnected services, and adopting leading technology for issuing tickets is an important part of this process, with the key smartcard a recent addition, designed to boost the customer experience.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>The contract builds on an existing relationship between GTR, its Go-Ahead Group parent company, and Worldline. GTR already uses Worldline onboard ticket issuing systems, and Go-Ahead Group recently procured 585 mobile onboard TIS units from Worldline.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Implementation of the new mobile system will begin in the fourth quarter and is set to complete by the end of 2017, with GTR to benefit from cost savings from the commencement of installation.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>The @Station service shares the same back office architecture as Worldline onboard TIS, so all mobile ticket sales data will be captured through one system. Using Worldline’s mobile and onboard systems in tandem also delivers operational synergies and efficiencies. Staff should quickly become familiar with the user interface, lowering training and support costs, and enabling flexibility in staff deployment.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;img src=&quot;/content/dam/worldline/images/blog/dots/horizontal/dot-line-700v3.png&quot;>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;blockquote>&lt;span class=&quot;block--featured--title&quot;>Alex Foulds, Business Improvement Director at Govia Thameslink Railway, said;&lt;/span> “&lt;i>As the UK’s largest rail franchise, utilising the most operationally-sound technology is critical to the logistical success of our network and the customer experience we offer. We are confident that Mobile POS for ticket issuing and retailing other products will improve passenger service, increase the speed of customer interaction, and enable payments to be processed faster. The agreement with Worldline comes as we work to improve our customers’ experience amid our transformation of the busiest part of UK’s rail network.”&lt;/i>&lt;b>&lt;/b>&lt;/blockquote>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;blockquote>&lt;span class=&quot;block--featured--title&quot;>Lisa Coleman, Managing Director for the Regional Business Unit UK and for MTS Germany &amp;amp; CEE said:&lt;/span> “&lt;i>I am thrilled that GTR has chosen Worldline to transform its ticket issuing and product retailing capabilities. Worldline has more than 30 years’ experience in rail retail with a product portfolio that spans online, consumer mobile app, on-board, and on-station channels. We also have a solid portfolio of operational systems. I look forward to a highly successful partnership.”&lt;/i>&lt;/blockquote>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;img src=&quot;/content/dam/worldline/images/blog/dots/horizontal/dot-line-700v3.png&quot;>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h3>Worldline Press contact:&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>3x1 Public Relations&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Karen Halley / Jackie McColl&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Email: khalley@3x1.com / jmccoll@3x1.com&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>0131 225 7700 / 0141 221 0707&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Govia Thameslink Railway contact:&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Email: press.office@gtrailway.com&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;ul>&#xa;&lt;li>Southern and Gatwick Express press office: 0203 750 2030&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>Thameslink and Great Northern press office: 0203 750 2031&lt;br>&#xa;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;/ul>&#xa;&lt;h3>About Worldline&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>Worldline [Euronext: WLN] is the European leader in the payments and transactional services industry. Worldline delivers new-generation services, enabling its customers to offer smooth and innovative solutions to the end consumer. Key actor for B2B2C industries, with nearly 45 years of experience, Worldline supports and contributes to the success of all businesses and administrative services in a perpetually evolving market. Worldline offers a unique and flexible business model built around a global and growing portfolio, thus enabling end-to-end support. Worldline activities are organized around three axes: Merchant Services, Mobility &amp;amp; e-Transactional Services and Financial Services including equensWorldline. Worldline employs more than 8,700 people worldwide, with estimated pro forma revenue of more than € 1.5 billion on a yearly basis. Worldline is an Atos company. &lt;a href=&quot;http://worldline.com/en-us/home.html&quot;>worldline.com&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h3>About Govia Thameslink Railway&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>Govia Thameslink Railway (GTR) is now the largest rail franchise in the UK in terms of passenger numbers, trains, revenue and staff, carrying more than 326 million passenger journeys per year, employing around 6,500 people and generating annual passenger revenues of approximately £1.3bn.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>The franchise operates Thameslink, Great Northern, Southern and Gatwick Express services as follows:&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;ul>&#xa;&lt;li>Thameslink – services between Bedford and Brighton, Luton/St Albans and Sutton, Wimbledon and Sevenoaks.&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>Great Northern – services between London and Welwyn, Hertford, Peterborough, Cambridge and King’s Lynn.&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>Southern – services between London and the Sussex coast (Brighton, Worthing, Eastbourne, Bognor Regis, Hastings) and parts of Surrey, Kent and Hampshire (Ashford International, Southampton, Portsmouth).&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;li>Gatwick Express – Fast, non-stop direct services between Gatwick Airport and London Victoria.&lt;/li>&#xa;&lt;/ul>&#xa;&lt;p>The GTR investment programme for stations includes funding for more CCTV, toilet refurbishments, new retail facilities, help points and car park improvements – as well as plans for increased motorcycle storage and improved transport integration.&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                        textIsRich="true"/>
                </column1>
            </grid>
        </content>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
