<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:contextHubPath="/etc/cloudsettings/default/contexthub"
        cq:contextHubSegmentsPath="/etc/segmentation/contexthub"
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2017-11-27T17:50:24.781+01:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="a598986"
        cq:lastReplicated="{Date}2017-11-27T15:05:27.095+01:00"
        cq:lastReplicatedBy="a598986"
        cq:lastReplicationAction="Deactivate"
        cq:tags="[blog:corporate]"
        cq:template="/apps/gotomarket/templates/blogarticle"
        jcr:description="Zanda Brivule-Jansone has devoted her entire 20-year professional career to the payments cards industry, with the last 10 years at the helm of First Data Baltics, now known as Worldline Baltics. In this role, she developed partnerships and nearshoring opportunities in the Nordics. Under Zanda’s leadership, Worldline Baltics has become the most professional and reliable payment card services provider in the Baltic countries, covering the whole card payments value chain."
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-11-23T10:08:12.028+01:00"
        jcr:lastModifiedBy="a598986"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:lockable,mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="The 3 key assets of Worldline’s Human Resources strategy that make the difference"
        jcr:uuid="5c3b1899-2b88-47c6-a3c6-35c747c66a36"
        sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/pages/blogarticle"
        authorImage="/content/dam/worldline/images/blog/author/gry3-80.png"
        authorName="Patrice Gry"
        authorText="HR Director"
        categories="[category:talents]"
        categories_x0040_TypeHint="String[]"
        color="#ffffff"
        creationDate="{Date}2017-09-06T15:44:00.000+02:00"
        hideInNav="false"
        imagePath="/content/dam/worldline/images/blog/header/build-your-career-header-v2.jpg"
        isExternalContactUsUrl="false"
        isExternalJoinUsUrl="false"
        isStickyContactHidden="false"
        noExtentionContactUs="false"
        noExtentionJoinUs="false"
        showbrand="false"
        showinfostrip="false"
        title="The 3 key assets of&#xd;&#xa;Worldline’s Human Resources strategy&#xd;&#xa;that make the difference">
        <head
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/head"/>
        <headlibs
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/headlibs"/>
        <header
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/header">
            <leftnavigation
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/leftnavigation"
                iconClass="iconClass2"/>
            <rightnavigation
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/rightnavigation"
                iconClass="iconClass2">
                <countrylistdropdown
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/countrylistdropdown"/>
                <languagedropdown
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/languagedropdown"/>
            </rightnavigation>
            <mainnav
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/mainnav"/>
            <infostrip
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/infostrip"/>
            <breadcrumbblog
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/breadcrumbblog"/>
        </header>
        <headerblog
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/headerblog"/>
        <singleauthor
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/singleauthor"/>
        <prshare
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/prshare"/>
        <stayintouch
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/stayintouch"/>
        <footer
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/footer">
            <sitemap
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/sitemap"/>
            <followus
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/followus"/>
            <newsletterform
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/newsletterform"/>
        </footer>
        <footlibs
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/footlibs"/>
        <copyright
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/copyright"/>
        <content
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/parsys">
            <richtext
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-09-07T14:33:40.318+02:00"
                jcr:createdBy="a646217"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-11-27T17:50:24.777+01:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="a598986"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/content/richtext"
                text="&lt;p>In our fast-changing, competitive and innovation-driven industry, our ability to &lt;b>attract, develop and retain the best talents&lt;/b> is a &lt;b>key success factor&lt;/b> in Worldline’s ambitious development strategy. As a result, our Human Resources strategy relies on &lt;b>three main differentiating assets&lt;/b> that have been consolidated throughout a &lt;b>45-year history of growth and innovation&lt;/b> and that are at the &lt;b>core of our DNA&lt;/b>:&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;span class=&quot;styled&quot;>A &lt;b>strong power of attraction&lt;/b> linked to a genuine pride and sense of belonging&lt;/span>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;span class=&quot;styled&quot;>A &lt;b>proven know-how in people’s integration&lt;/b>&lt;/span>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;span class=&quot;styled&quot;>A &lt;b>recognized expert network&lt;/b>&lt;/span>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;blockquote style=&quot;color: #0066A1;&quot;>“The diversity of our professions, the scope of our business and technological areas, the societal impacts of our solutions and the career development opportunities are the core ingredients of our recipe to attract and retain talents.”&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;/blockquote>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>During the past two years, we have made extensive efforts to &lt;b>reinforce our employer brand&lt;/b> and to develop &lt;b>close relations with the leading Engineering and Business Schools and Universities&lt;/b>. This has resulted in the strengthening of our &lt;b>attractiveness&lt;/b>, especially towards &lt;b>juniors&lt;/b>, who are the &lt;b>core target of our hiring policy&lt;/b>. Our strong ambition in this area is reflected through our commitment to be &lt;b>cited in 5 employer brand studies by 2020&lt;/b>, a &lt;b>key objective of our TRUST 2020 Corporate Social Responsibility&lt;/b> long-term program. And this strategy has already paid off, as confirmed by the &lt;b>“Best Chile 2017” award&lt;/b> and the &lt;b>“Happy Trainee 2016-2017” label&lt;/b> we obtained.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>One of the key pillars of our Talent acquisition strategy is the &lt;b>wide range of job opportunities offered by Worldline&lt;/b>. As a &lt;b>leader in the payment industry and a key player of the digital transformation&lt;/b>, we are well-positioned to &lt;b>cover numerous business activities in all industries&lt;/b> and to &lt;b>address emerging technological areas&lt;/b>, including &lt;b>payments&lt;/b>, &lt;b>Internet of Things&lt;/b>, &lt;b>Artificial Intelligence&lt;/b> and &lt;b>Blockchain&lt;/b> among others. Moreover, our &lt;b>build-to-run business model&lt;/b> allows us to embrace &lt;b>all the professions of the IT value chain&lt;/b>. Finally, the &lt;b>societal impacts&lt;/b> and value of our projects and solutions also constitute a real &lt;b>source of attractiveness, motivation and empowerment&lt;/b> for new joiners.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Another fundamental driver of our successful “attract and retain the best talents” strategy is the &lt;b>priority&lt;/b> we give to &lt;b>internal mobility&lt;/b> and &lt;b>promotion&lt;/b>. Thanks to our mobility and our learning &amp;amp; development policies supported by in-house tools, programs and best practices, we offer all our employees the opportunity to &lt;b>grow, change jobs regularly and take wider responsibilities to meet their professional goals by developing their own career path&lt;/b> within the company.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;blockquote style=&quot;color: #0066A1;&quot;>“Any visitor who experiences Worldline from the inside will be astonished by the pride of belonging and the engagement of our teams.”&amp;nbsp;&lt;/blockquote>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>We are particularly proud to emphasize the &lt;b>strong sense of belonging&lt;/b> &lt;b>of our employees&lt;/b> as a &lt;b>core component of our cultural identity&lt;/b>. This is notably expressed through the &lt;b>genuine family and team spirit&lt;/b>, &lt;b>engagement&lt;/b> and &lt;b>professionalism&lt;/b> demonstrated by our teams.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>And the proof is in the figures! Indeed, for the past 5 years, we have obtained the &lt;b>best results (nearly 70% on average)&lt;/b> on the &lt;b>“Pride” dimension&lt;/b> questions of the &lt;b>Great Place to Work&lt;/b>® (GPTW) annual survey that measures &lt;b>our employees’ satisfaction&lt;/b>. &lt;b>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b>Considering that o&lt;b>ur employees’ well-being&lt;/b> is an &lt;b>essential part of our responsible employer approach&lt;/b> and a &lt;b>key driver for engagement and performance&lt;/b> in the long term, we have committed to &lt;b>increase our employees’ satisfaction as part of our TRUST 2020 ambition&lt;/b>. And our efforts in making Worldline a great place to work through our &lt;b>wellbeing@worldline dedicated program&lt;/b> have already been rewarded by a &lt;b>7-point gain in the overall employee satisfaction&lt;/b> in 2016.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>This sense of belonging is also reflected through our &lt;b>12-year seniority average&lt;/b> and a &lt;b>relatively low turnover rate for our sector in Europe of c. 5% in 2016&lt;/b>. The &lt;b>participation rate of 23% in our last employee share plan&lt;/b> also testifies to our &lt;b>employees’ trust in the future of the company&lt;/b>.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;blockquote style=&quot;color: #0066A1;&quot;>“Our strong experience and proven know-how in people’s integration is a valuable asset to support our group’s external growth strategy.”&lt;/blockquote>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Building on our long history marked by significant acquisitions, we have developed a &lt;b>real and solid expertise in newcomers’ welcoming and integration&lt;/b>.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>From an HR perspective, a successful integration depends on our ability to address the following major challenges in a consistent manner:&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;span class=&quot;styled&quot;>Share a &lt;b>common balanced project&lt;/b>&lt;/span>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;span class=&quot;styled&quot;>&lt;b>Anticipate&lt;/b>, at an early stage, the &lt;b>preparation and set-up of the integration’s related processes and organization&lt;/b> through a shared methodology between mixed teams &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;span class=&quot;styled&quot;>&lt;b>Monitor&amp;nbsp; the progress of the integration plan&lt;/b>, especially the &lt;b>implementation of Worldline HR tools&lt;/b> to spread our best practices through a &lt;b>structured roadmap&lt;/b> and a set of KPIs&lt;/span>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;span class=&quot;styled&quot;>&lt;b>Support the integration process&lt;/b> through &lt;b>regular communication&lt;/b> on the key milestones and a &lt;b>global change management approach&lt;/b>&lt;/span>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>This proven know-how is &lt;b>absolutely fundamental&lt;/b> to ensure the &lt;b>day 1 organization readiness&lt;/b> and a &lt;b>seamless onboarding of the new teams&lt;/b> on the Worldline journey allowing our new joiners to be immediately infused with our culture and way of life.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;blockquote style=&quot;color: #0066A1;&quot;>“Spreading innovation through our recognized expert network represents a key success factor in our mission to create value for our clients through inspired and advanced solutions.”&lt;/blockquote>&#xa;&lt;p>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Innovation &lt;/b>is at the &lt;b>heart of our value proposal&lt;/b> to &lt;b>invent&lt;/b>, &lt;b>design &lt;/b>and &lt;b>offer our clients inspiring and state-of-the-art next-generation solutions&lt;/b>, &lt;b>suited to their business needs&lt;/b>. To promote this, we rely on a &lt;b>community of 250 highly skilled and talented experts&lt;/b> focused on our &lt;b>8 core technological domains&lt;/b> and structured around &lt;b>4 levels, from Junior to Fellow&lt;/b>.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Through this &lt;b>“made by Worldline” expert community&lt;/b>, we provide our experts with a &lt;b>nurturing and stimulating environment&lt;/b> to develop an &lt;b>innovative mindset&lt;/b> and &lt;b>facilitate expertise sharing across the organization&lt;/b>. This includes taking an &lt;b>alternative approach to the tradition of promoting&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xa;employees to managers and instead oﬀering specific career paths and perspectives that enable experts to be rewarded and recognized as they continue to advance in their technical discipline. Consequently, a specific Compensation and Benefits policy has been defined for the experts with, in particular, the allocation of dedicated time to ensure a technology watch and research on hot technological topics or to attend major international conferences such as Java One or Google I/O.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>The expert community also constitutes the real catalyst to irrigate, evangelize and fertilize the entire company through innovations, new technologies and solutions.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Additionally, special events are organized regularly to spread innovation and expertise widely across the company such as Expert Days, international TechForums, in-house Innovation Awards, called Win Awards, and project contests for our very own “Win Lift” incubator, gathering more than 1,500 Worldliners passionate about innovation.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>In the fast evolving world of payments and e-transactions, our expert community is therefore an unquestionable crucial asset to keep our competitive advantage and to support our expansion.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>We hope this article has triggered your willingness to learn more about the Worldline journey and we kindly invite you to stay tuned to discover soon new articles and interviews about our HR best practices.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>To learn more about our hiring and internal mobility approaches, feel free to have a look at the following interviews:&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;span class=&quot;styled&quot;>&lt;a href=&quot;http://worldline.com/en-us/home/inside-worldline/2016/november/Worldline-expands-its-people-s-professional-horizons.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>Worldline expands its people professional horizons&lt;/a>&lt;/span>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;span class=&quot;styled&quot;>&lt;a href=&quot;http://worldline.com/en-us/home/inside-worldline/2016/september/the-human-capital-the-key-to-our-success.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>The human capital, the key of our success&lt;/a>&lt;/span>&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                textIsRich="true"/>
        </content>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
