<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:contextHubPath="/etc/cloudsettings/default/contexthub"
        cq:contextHubSegmentsPath="/etc/segmentation/contexthub"
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2017-11-27T17:47:53.971+01:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="fr20437"
        cq:lastReplicated="{Date}2017-11-29T17:32:38.430+01:00"
        cq:lastReplicatedBy="fr20437"
        cq:lastReplicationAction="Activate"
        cq:tags="[article:]"
        cq:template="/apps/gotomarket/templates/releasearticle"
        jcr:description="4 September 2017 – Bezons, Worldline [Euronext:WLN], European leader &#xd;&#xa;in the payments and transactional services industry announces that its &#xd;&#xa;subsidiary, equensWorldline SE, was selected by three major banks in the &#xd;&#xa;Netherlands as their infrastructure provider for Instant Payments. This &#xd;&#xa;collaboration facilitates the next step in the process of realizing a real-time &#xd;&#xa;payment system. In Europe, several preparations are being made for &#xd;&#xa;Instant Payments, but the pace and the method vary per country. The &#xd;&#xa;Netherlands is one of the first countries that started the development of &#xd;&#xa;these real-time payments."
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-11-27T17:47:53.967+01:00"
        jcr:lastModifiedBy="fr20437"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Three major banks in the Netherlands select equensWorldline as infrastructure provider for Instant Payments"
        jcr:uuid="83f653eb-9106-451b-869c-259a4763d863"
        sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/pages/releasearticle"
        brand="worldline"
        categories="[article:]"
        categories_x0040_TypeHint="String[]"
        creationDate="{Date}2017-09-04T17:47:00.000+02:00"
        hideInNav="false"
        imagePath="/content/dam/gotomarket/uploads/bg-header-industries.jpg"
        isExternalContactUsUrl="false"
        isExternalJoinUsUrl="false"
        isStickyContactHidden="false"
        keywords="Three major banks, Netherlands, equensWorldline, infrastructure provider, Instant Payments&#xd;&#xa;"
        noExtentionContactUs="false"
        noExtentionJoinUs="false"
        showbrand="false"
        showinfostrip="false">
        <head
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/head"/>
        <headlibs
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/headlibs"/>
        <header
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/header">
            <leftnavigation
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/leftnavigation"
                iconClass="iconClass2"/>
            <rightnavigation
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/rightnavigation"
                iconClass="iconClass2">
                <countrylistdropdown
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/countrylistdropdown"/>
                <languagedropdown
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/languagedropdown"/>
            </rightnavigation>
            <mainnav
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/mainnav"/>
            <infostrip
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/infostrip"/>
            <breadcrumb
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/breadcrumb"/>
        </header>
        <headerpage
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/headerpage"/>
        <releasetitle
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/releasetitle"/>
        <key
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/parsys">
            <releasekeymessages
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/releasekeymessages"/>
        </key>
        <releasedescription
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/releasedescription"/>
        <prshare
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/prshare"/>
        <footer
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/footer">
            <sitemap
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/sitemap"/>
            <followus
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/followus"/>
            <newsletterform
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/newsletterform"/>
        </footer>
        <footlibs
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/footlibs"/>
        <copyright
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/copyright"/>
        <content
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/parsys">
            <grid
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-08-30T10:47:59.727+02:00"
                jcr:createdBy="a646217"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-08-30T10:47:59.727+02:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="a646217"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/layout/grid">
                <column1
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/parsys">
                    <richtext
                        jcr:created="{Date}2017-08-30T10:48:06.075+02:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="a646217"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-11-27T17:47:36.249+01:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="fr20437"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/content/richtext"
                        text="&lt;p>&lt;b>4 September 2017 – Bezons, Worldline [Euronext:WLN], European leader&amp;nbsp;in the payments and transactional services industry announces that its&amp;nbsp;subsidiary, equensWorldline SE, was selected by three major banks in the&amp;nbsp;Netherlands as their infrastructure provider for Instant Payments. This&amp;nbsp;collaboration facilitates the next step in the process of realizing a real-time&amp;nbsp;payment system. In Europe, several preparations are being made for&amp;nbsp;Instant Payments, but the pace and the method vary per country. The&amp;nbsp;Netherlands is one of the first countries that started the development of&amp;nbsp;these real-time payments.&lt;/b>&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>equensWorldline will provide a new European and global payments infrastructure that allows&amp;nbsp;payments to be processed instantly so that the recipient immediately receives the money. These&amp;nbsp;real-time payments will be available around the clock, 365 days a year, including weekends and&amp;nbsp;holidays. This means that it will always immediately be clear whether a transfer from the payer to&amp;nbsp;the recipient has succeeded. That is beneficial to consumers who can immediately have their&amp;nbsp;purchase, but also for merchants who receive the money instantly. Instant Payments therefore&amp;nbsp;provide a better cash flow and reduced risk for businesses.&amp;nbsp;Payment services provider equensWorldline is on schedule to deliver the infrastructure for Instant&amp;nbsp;Payments on time. &amp;quot;The program to deliver Instant Payments in the Netherlands is well underway,&amp;nbsp;and with the choice of an infrastructure provider, the three major banks took a huge step,&amp;quot; explains&amp;nbsp;Alessandro Baroni, CMO equensWorldline. &amp;quot;At equensWorldline, we are ready. The development of&amp;nbsp;the infrastructure is completed and the results of the tests we have performed to date are looking&amp;nbsp;good.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp;The next step is to connect the three large Dutch banks to equensWorldline's infrastructure. The&amp;nbsp;projects to achieve this have been started and are progressing prosperously. According to the plans&amp;nbsp;of the Dutch banking community, the first Instant Payments will be processed in 2019 when the full&amp;nbsp;roll-out will take place so that real-time payments become a reality in the Netherlands.&amp;nbsp;Bart van de Sande, head of Operations Transaction Banking ABN AMRO: &amp;quot;The best seamless&amp;nbsp;payment experience; that is what ABN AMRO wants to offer its customers. As we expect Instant&amp;nbsp;Payments to become the 'new normal', we will deliver this new service as fast as possible. We are&amp;nbsp;delighted that equensWorldline is one of our partners in realizing our ambition.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp;Roel Popping, Director Payments ING Nederland: &amp;quot;Instant Payments are the future in payments and&amp;nbsp;ING wants to offer a superior solution to its customers. We selected equensWorldline because of&amp;nbsp;their positive track record and flexibility in supporting the Dutch market.&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;quot;Real-time is the future of payments processing and we need to offer our customers superior&amp;nbsp;solutions that keep us competitive with the new entrants in financial services,&amp;quot; said Erik Kwakkel,&amp;nbsp;Executive Vice President Payment Services, Rabobank. &amp;quot;We selected equensWorldline because its&amp;nbsp;solution offers the high performance and availability capabilities we seek, while it is cost efficient&amp;nbsp;and also has the flexibility to support the requirements in the Dutch community&amp;quot;&amp;nbsp;Michael Steinbach, CEO of equensWorldline: &amp;quot;By expanding our portfolio with this complete Instant&amp;nbsp;Payment service, we demonstrate our continued focus to cater for the full spectrum of our clients'&amp;nbsp;current and future needs. This seamlessly fits our European strategy, aimed at supporting our&amp;nbsp;clients in the challenges they are facing in the rapidly developing European, and more and more,&amp;nbsp;global payments market, in which responsiveness, customer value and the capability to innovate are&amp;nbsp;of the essence.&amp;quot;&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h3>About Worldline&lt;br>&#xa;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>Worldline [Euronext: WLN] is the European leader in the payments and transactional services industry. Worldline delivers new-generation services, enabling its customers to offer smooth and innovative solutions to the end consumer. Key actor for B2B2C industries, with nearly 45 years of experience, Worldline supports and contributes to the success of all businesses and administrative services in a perpetually evolving market. Worldline offers a unique and flexible business model built around a global and growing portfolio, thus enabling end-to-end support. Worldline activities are organized around three axes: Merchant Services, Mobility &amp;amp; e-Transactional Services and Financial Services including equensWorldline. Worldline employs more than 8,700 people worldwide, with estimated pro forma revenue of more than € 1.5 billion on a yearly basis. Worldline is an Atos company. worldline.com&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h3>About equensWorldline&lt;br>&#xa;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>equensWorldline is the pan-European leader in payment services. Being part of the Worldline Group,&amp;nbsp;the company combines long-standing proven expertise in traditional mass payment systems&amp;nbsp;(issuing, acquiring, intra- and interbank payment processing) and innovative e-commerce and&amp;nbsp;mobile payment solutions. Building on more than 50 years of experience equensWorldline services a&amp;nbsp;broad, international client base in numerous countries across Europe. Clients rely on&amp;nbsp;equensWorldline's expertise to anticipate European regulatory changes, benefit from transformative&amp;nbsp;technologies, optimize processes, ensure operational excellence and manage risk and fraud. The&amp;nbsp;company's unparalleled footprint makes equensWorldline a cost-efficient and competitive business&amp;nbsp;partner for seamless, secure and efficient payment solutions.&amp;nbsp;equensworldline.comInterested in our Instant Payments solutions? Click &lt;a href=&quot;http://secure.equensworldline.com/instant-payments/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;>here&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h3>equensWorldline Press Contact&lt;br>&#xa;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Marcel Woutersen (NL)&lt;/b>T +31 (0)88 385 54 27M +31 (0)6 29 05 08 71E marcel.woutersen@equensworldline.com&lt;br>&#xa;&amp;nbsp;&lt;b>Annemieke Lambregts (NL)&lt;/b>T +31 (0)88 385 50 27M +31 (0)6 50 21 30 91E annemieke.lambregts@equensworldline.com&lt;br>&#xa;&amp;nbsp;&lt;b>Jörg Richter (DE)&lt;/b>T +49 (0)69 256 60362M +49 (0)172 - 6 13 95 97E joerg.richter@equensworldline.com&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                        textIsRich="true"/>
                </column1>
            </grid>
        </content>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
