<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:contextHubPath="/etc/cloudsettings/default/contexthub"
        cq:contextHubSegmentsPath="/etc/segmentation/contexthub"
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2017-11-27T18:22:00.610+01:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="fr20437"
        cq:lastReplicated="{Date}2017-11-27T18:28:29.066+01:00"
        cq:lastReplicatedBy="fr20437"
        cq:lastReplicationAction="Activate"
        cq:tags="[article:business,article:general]"
        cq:template="/apps/gotomarket/templates/releasearticle"
        jcr:description="Munich/Paris, 25 March 2014 - The integration into the PAY.ON Payment Gateway facilitates Worldline the immediate access into a high-performance payment gateway, the processing of transactions in more than 100 countries,and access to more than 350 payment providers and 150 payment brands over a single API. With this enriched geographical coverage, Worldline will be able to even better satisfy the growing needs of its customers, currently spread in 17 countries, and leverage their business globally: Worldline clients can now easily connect to a wide range of foreign acquirers and payment methods for processing of local payment transactions worldwide."
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-08-28T17:39:02.752+02:00"
        jcr:lastModifiedBy="a101309"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Worldline chooses PAY.ON’s Payment Gateway to extend the reach of its international acceptance"
        jcr:uuid="ecfd79af-bcff-4828-a990-19a186039908"
        sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/pages/releasearticle"
        brand="worldline"
        categories_x0040_TypeHint="String[]"
        creationDate="{Date}2017-08-28T10:00:00.000+02:00"
        hideInNav="false"
        imagePath="/content/dam/gotomarket/uploads/bg-header-industries.jpg"
        showbrand="false"
        showinfostrip="false">
        <head
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/head"/>
        <headlibs
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/headlibs"/>
        <header
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/header">
            <leftnavigation
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/leftnavigation"
                iconClass="iconClass2"/>
            <rightnavigation
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/rightnavigation"
                iconClass="iconClass2">
                <countrylistdropdown
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/countrylistdropdown"/>
                <languagedropdown
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/languagedropdown"/>
            </rightnavigation>
            <mainnav
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/mainnav"/>
            <infostrip
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/infostrip"/>
            <breadcrumb
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/breadcrumb"/>
        </header>
        <headerpage
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/headerpage"/>
        <releasetitle
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/releasetitle"/>
        <key
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/parsys">
            <releasekeymessages
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/releasekeymessages"/>
        </key>
        <releasedescription
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/releasedescription"/>
        <prshare
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/prshare"/>
        <footer
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/footer">
            <sitemap
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/sitemap"/>
            <followus
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/followus"/>
            <newsletterform
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/newsletterform"/>
        </footer>
        <footlibs
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/footlibs"/>
        <copyright
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/copyright"/>
        <content
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/parsys">
            <grid
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-08-28T17:33:09.560+02:00"
                jcr:createdBy="a101309"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-08-28T17:33:09.560+02:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="a101309"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/layout/grid">
                <column1 jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured">
                    <richtext
                        jcr:created="{Date}2017-08-28T17:33:18.697+02:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="a101309"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-08-29T14:50:49.484+02:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="a101309"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/content/richtext"
                        text="&lt;p>PAY.ON, worldwide leading provider of Web-based, omnichannel payment infrastructure systems, and Worldline, Atos subsidiary for e-payment services, announce a premium strategic partnership to enlarge Worldline’s international e-payment acceptance coverage. With the partnership, Worldline strengthens its worldwide positioning to better support its customers when operating cross-border and entering new markets and countries. With Atos Worldline, PAY.ON gains another partner, delivering its clients a further connection to the French market.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Munich/Paris, 25 March 2014 - The integration into the PAY.ON Payment Gateway facilitates Worldline the immediate access into a high-performance payment gateway, the processing of transactions in more than 100 countries,and access to more than 350 payment providers and 150 payment brands over a single API. With this enriched geographical coverage, Worldline will be able to even better satisfy the growing needs of its customers, currently spread in 17 countries, and leverage their business globally: Worldline clients can now easily connect to a wide range of foreign acquirers and payment methods for processing of local payment transactions worldwide.&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;blockquote>&lt;span class=&quot;block--featured--title&quot;>Wolfgang Berner, Vice President Product and Integration at PAY.ON, said:&lt;/span> “We are delighted to join forces with Worldline, an international and globally active partner. Our Payment Gateway enables Worldline to expand its global presence within a short time frame and without regional-specific payment barriers whilst delivering the highest quality and security standards. Both parties mutually benefit from the partnership due to greater market penetration and access to new client segments.”&lt;/blockquote>&#xa;&lt;blockquote>&lt;span class=&quot;block--featured--title&quot;>Christophe Duquenne, COO and Head of Merchant Services from Worldline, added: &lt;/span>“We have a strong commitment to providing the most advanced and innovative solutions to our customers. Our connection to PAY.ON Payment Gateway will extend our geographical coverage for Merchant Services Online Payment globally, so we can offer our customers a wide range of payment methods and worldwide acquirer connectivity.”&lt;/blockquote>&#xa;&lt;h3>About Worldline&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>Worldline, an Atos subsidiary, is the European leader and a global player in the payments and transactional services industry. Worldline delivers new-generation services, enabling its customers to offer smooth and innovative solutions to the end consumer. Key actor for B2B2C industries, with 40 years of experience, Worldline is ideally positioned to support and contribute to the success of all businesses and administrative services in a perpetually evolving market. Worldline offers a unique and flexible business model built around a global and growing portfolio, thus enabling end-to-end support. Worldline activities are organised around three axes: Merchant Services &amp;amp; Terminals, Mobility &amp;amp; e-Transactional Services, Financial Processing Services &amp;amp; Software Licensing. In 2013, Worldline’s activities within the Atos Group generated (pro forma) revenues of 1.11 billion euros. The company employs more than 7,200 people worldwide.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;a title=&quot;www.worldline.com&quot; href=&quot;http://www.worldline.com&quot;>www.worldline.com&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h3>About PAY.ON&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>PAY.ON AG is a worldwide leading provider of payment infrastructure systems whose cloud services cover all aspects and requirements of modern, globally networked payment processing. As a white-label provider, PAY.ON guarantees full independence for its customers (PSPs, ISOs, acquirers and financial institutions). PAY.ON is an omnichannel platform which, in its full capacity, enables users to activate their system with all the relevant payment and risk management processes on an ad hoc basis, including global connectivity and the latest fraud and chargeback prevention – and to expand their system at any time with external tools and market-tested PAY.ON services, such as rapid merchant onboarding and mobile payments. As a result, business cases of any complexity can be strategically expanded, outsourced in their entirety or realised in a way that saves money, time and other resources. For the prompt improved connectivity of existing systems, the modular PAY.ON gateway makes it possible to connect directly to more than 350 system-relevant payment service providers around the world – and more than 150 types of payment – via a single API. With its gateway, PAY.ON therefore accelerates global provider availability more than any other network. All PAY.ON systems guarantee complete compliance with internationally binding PCI and security standards and are operated with a high level of reliability from in-house data centres. Further information can be found at &lt;a title=&quot;www.payon.com&quot; href=&quot;http://www.payon.com&quot;>www.payon.com&lt;/a>.&lt;b>&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h3>Media contacts:&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Worldline&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xa;+31 6 30 27 26 11&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;a title=&quot;Jose.devries@atos.net&quot; href=&quot;mailto:Jose.devries@atos.net&quot;>Jose.devries@atos.net&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>PAY.ON AG&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xa;Annett van de Bunt&lt;br>&#xa;+49 (0)89 4523 0552&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;a title=&quot;press@payon.com&quot; href=&quot;mailto:press@payon.com&quot;>press@payon.com&lt;/a>&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;a title=&quot;www.payon.com&quot; href=&quot;http://www.payon.com&quot;>www.payon.com&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                        textIsRich="true"/>
                </column1>
            </grid>
        </content>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
