<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2017-10-16T18:04:44.880+02:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="fr20437"
        cq:lastReplicated="{Date}2017-10-30T17:58:23.647+01:00"
        cq:lastReplicatedBy="a631192"
        cq:lastReplicationAction="Activate"
        cq:template="/apps/gotomarket/templates/content"
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Terms of use"
        jcr:uuid="d65d6463-a736-40da-bb39-017fa489beda"
        sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/pages/content"
        carouselItems="\{&quot;imagePath&quot;:&quot;/content/dam/gotomarket/bg-header-solutions.jpg&quot;,&quot;title&quot;:&quot;&quot;,&quot;subtitle&quot;:&quot;&quot;,&quot;description&quot;:&quot;&quot;,&quot;link&quot;:&quot;&quot;}"
        keywords="Terms of use">
        <head
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/head"/>
        <headlibs
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/headlibs"/>
        <header
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/header">
            <leftnavigation
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/leftnavigation"
                iconClass="iconClass2"/>
            <rightnavigation
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/rightnavigation"
                iconClass="iconClass2">
                <countrylistdropdown
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/countrylistdropdown"/>
                <languagedropdown
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/languagedropdown"/>
            </rightnavigation>
            <mainnav
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/mainnav"/>
            <infostrip
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/infostrip"/>
            <content
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/parsys">
                <search
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/search"/>
            </content>
            <breadcrumb
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/breadcrumb"/>
        </header>
        <headerpage
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/headerpage"/>
        <contactus
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/contactus"/>
        <footer
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/footer">
            <sitemap
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/sitemap"/>
            <followus
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/followus"/>
            <newsletterform
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/newsletterform"/>
        </footer>
        <footlibs
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/footlibs"/>
        <copyright
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/copyright"/>
        <content
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/parsys">
            <section
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-10-16T18:04:14.464+02:00"
                jcr:createdBy="fr20437"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-10-16T18:04:14.464+02:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="fr20437"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/layout/section">
                <items jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured">
                    <grid
                        jcr:created="{Date}2017-08-31T10:24:28.298+02:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="a646217"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-08-31T10:24:28.298+02:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="a646217"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/layout/grid">
                        <column1
                            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/parsys">
                            <titleh2
                                jcr:created="{Date}2017-10-16T18:03:05.410+02:00"
                                jcr:createdBy="fr20437"
                                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-10-16T18:04:29.511+02:00"
                                jcr:lastModifiedBy="fr20437"
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/content/titleH2"
                                showDots="true"
                                title="Terms of use"
                                titleAlignment="left"/>
                            <richtext
                                jcr:created="{Date}2017-08-31T10:24:39.202+02:00"
                                jcr:createdBy="a646217"
                                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-10-16T18:04:44.878+02:00"
                                jcr:lastModifiedBy="fr20437"
                                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/content/richtext"
                                text="&lt;p>You are now connected to the Worldline public Internet Site. The information and content contained herein are provided subject to the following Terms and Conditions and your access to this web site and continued usage constitutes complete acceptance of these terms and conditions: .&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&#xd;&#xa;&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>The present site is intended to provide information about Worldline and its subsidiaries and affiliates (&amp;quot;Worldline&amp;quot;), its organization, the products and services offered by its divisions, and its share performance. However, this information represents only a presentation of Worldline's products and services and is not contractually binding. To enter into any form of contractual agreement, please contact the parent company or one of its subsidiaries directly.&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&#xd;&#xa;&lt;br>&#xd;&#xa;&#xd;&#xa;Unless otherwise stated, the contents of this site including, but not limited to, the text and images contained herein and their arrangement are the property of Worldline. All trademarks used or referred to in this website are the property of their respective owners.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Nothing contained in this site shall be construed as conferring any license or right to any copyright, patent, trademark or other proprietary interest of Worldline or any third party. This site and the content provided in this site, including, but not limited to, text, graphics, images, audio, video, html code, buttons, and, may not be copied, reproduced, republished, uploaded, posted, transmitted, or distributed in any way, without the prior written consent of Worldline, except that you may download, display, and print one copy of the materials on any single computer solely for your personal, non-commercial use, provided that you do not modify the material in any way and you keep intact all copyright, trademark, and other proprietary notices.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>The information provided on this site is free of charge and for informational purposes only and does not create a business or professional services relationship between you and Worldline. Links on this site may lead to services or sites not operated by Worldline. No judgment or warranty is made with respect to such other services or sites and Worldline takes no responsibility for such other sites or services. A link to another site or service is not an endorsement of that site or service. Any use you make of the information provided on this site, or any site or service linked to by this site, is at your own risk.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Although Worldline uses reasonable efforts to include accurate and up-to-date information in this web site, this web site may include inaccuracies, outdated information or typographical errors. Therefore, Worldline makes no warranties or representations as to the accuracy or completeness of any information contained herein. Further, Worldline assumes no liability, obligation or responsibility for any errors or omissions in the content of this site.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>The names, images, logos and pictures identifying Worldline's services are proprietary marks of Worldline and/or its affiliates. References made while using this web site to any third party provided information, content, goods, products, process or service by trade name, trademark, manufacturer or otherwise does not necessarily constitute or imply the endorsement, approval or recommendation thereof or connection therewith by Worldline. Further, this web site may be linked to other web sites, which are not under the control of and are not maintained by Worldline. Worldline has not reviewed any or all of the sites linked to this site and Worldline is not responsible for the content of those sites or any of the off-site pages or any other sites linked to those sites. Worldline is providing these links to you only as a convenience, and the inclusion of any link to such sites does not imply endorsement by Worldline of those sites.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Worldline does not claim ownership of the materials you provide through this website, including but not limited to feedback and suggestions, or posts, uploads, inputs or other submissions. Worldline shall not be liable or held accountable for the content or views expressed in such materials provided by you. Worldline reserves the right at all times, in its sole discretion, to screen content submitted by you and to edit, move, delete, and/or refuse to accept any content that in Worldline's judgment violates these Terms of Use or is otherwise unacceptable or inappropriate, whether for legal or other reasons.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>By submitting material on this web site, you grant Worldline, and anyone authorized by Worldline, a royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable, non-exclusive, unrestricted, worldwide license to use, copy, modify, transmit, sell, exploit, create derivative works from, distribute, and/or publicly perform or display such material, in whole or in part, in any manner or medium (whether now known or hereafter developed), for any purpose that Worldline may choose.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Your use of and browsing in this web site is at your own risk. Neither Worldline nor any other party involved in creating, producing, or delivering the site is liable for any direct, incidental, consequential, indirect, or punitive damages arising out of your access to, or use of, this site. Without limiting the foregoing, everything on this site is provided to you &amp;quot;as is&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;as available&amp;quot; without warranty of any kind, either expressed or implied, including, but not limited to, the implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or noninfringement of intellectual property rights of third parties.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Worldline may make modifications, improvements, corrections and/or changes to this web site and these Terms and Conditions at any time with reasonable notice.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Worldline may collect data logs of individuals surfing on Worldline website, with the purpose of understanding aggregate usage of features and pages. For this very purpose Worldline uses Google Analytics. In order to avoid the collection of your Personal Data by Google, Worldline has set up the tool in a manner which prevents the collection of IP addresses. Neither Worldline nor Google are able to identify individuals activity.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Addition Personal data can also be collected as a result of the subscription to the newsletter or to the Worldline' Premium Services. These Personal Data are processed by Worldline solely to deliver the appropriate support and service. None of these data will be shared with third parties.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Because data protection and security matters, the Worldline website is hosted in the European Union in order to guarantee an appropriate level of protection to all data that are collected and processed. Application support may be made from Worldline India. The transfers resulting from such support would be framed with the EU model clauses in order to provide an appropriate level of protection.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>When visiting our website, cookies are installed on the computer to allow us improving the way our websites works for example by making sure users are finding what they need easily. If you don't agree with the use of such cookies, you can set up your browser to limit or exclude their use.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Data subjects whose Personal Data are collected have a right to request access, amendment or erasure of their Personal Data. To exercise this right, Data subject can contact &lt;a>infoWL@worldline.com&lt;/a>&lt;a>.&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>In the event that any portion of these Terms and Conditions is held to be unenforceable, the unenforceable portion shall be construed in accordance with applicable law as nearly as possible to reflect the original intentions of the parties and the remainder of the provisions shall remain in full force and effect.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Worldline's failure to insist upon or enforce strict performance of any provision of this Agreement shall not be construed as a waiver of any provision or right. Neither the course of conduct between any party referred to herein nor trade practice shall act to modify any provision of these Terms and Conditions.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>These Terms and Conditions shall be governed by and construed in accordance with French law. Any cause of action against Worldline must be commenced in France.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&#xd;&#xa;&lt;h3>Press Releases&lt;/h3>&#xd;&#xa;&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Worldline press releases are presented on this web site for historical purposes only. The information provided by Worldline was accurate at the time of release, subject to the disclaimer about forward-looking statements, which was printed concurrently with the announcement. Investors should not assume that statements made in these documents remain in effect at a later time. Worldline does not review past postings to determine whether they remain accurate, and information contained in such postings may be superseded. Worldline disclaims any obligation to update the statements or press releases. The financial information that may be accessed through this page speaks only as of the particular date or dates of its origination. Such information may have become out of date. Worldline does not undertake any obligation, and disclaims any duty, to update any of the information available through this page. Worldline's future financial performance is subject to various trends, risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ materially from those expressed in any forward-looking statements. The trends, risks and uncertainties that could affect Worldline's future financial results are discussed more fully in Worldline's reports filed with the AMF, including Worldline's Annual Report for the most recent fiscal year.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>IF THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS ARE NOT ACCEPTED IN FULL, THE USE OF THIS WEB SITE MUST BE TERMINATED IMMEDIATELY.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>Atos, the Atos logo, Atos Codex, Atos Consulting, Atos Worldgrid, Bull, Canopy, equensWorldline, Unify, Worldline and Zero Email are registered trademarks of the Atos group.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>worldline.com is registered and owned by Worldline SA, a French limited company (&amp;quot;&lt;b>société anonyme&lt;/b>&amp;quot;), duly organised and validly existing under the laws of France having its registered office at River Ouest 80, Quai Voltaire, 95870 Bezons, France whose company number at the Commercial registry of Pontoise is 378 901 946.&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&#xd;&#xa;&lt;p>30 April 2014&lt;/p>&#xd;&#xa;&#xd;&#xa;"
                                textIsRich="true"/>
                        </column1>
                    </grid>
                </items>
            </section>
        </content>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
