<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<jcr:root xmlns:sling="http://sling.apache.org/jcr/sling/1.0" xmlns:cq="http://www.day.com/jcr/cq/1.0" xmlns:jcr="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/1.0" xmlns:mix="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/mix/1.0" xmlns:nt="http://www.jcp.org/jcr/nt/1.0"
    jcr:primaryType="cq:Page">
    <jcr:content
        cq:contextHubPath="/etc/cloudsettings/default/contexthub"
        cq:contextHubSegmentsPath="/etc/segmentation/contexthub"
        cq:lastModified="{Date}2017-11-27T18:21:26.091+01:00"
        cq:lastModifiedBy="fr20437"
        cq:lastReplicated="{Date}2017-11-27T18:28:26.356+01:00"
        cq:lastReplicatedBy="fr20437"
        cq:lastReplicationAction="Activate"
        cq:tags="[article:general]"
        cq:template="/apps/gotomarket/templates/releasearticle"
        jcr:description="Paris, 7 may 2014 - Worldline announces today the registration of its document de base with the French Autorité des marchés financiers (AMF) on 6 May 2014 under number I.14 - 027 ."
        jcr:isCheckedOut="{Boolean}true"
        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-08-29T17:06:20.845+02:00"
        jcr:lastModifiedBy="a101309"
        jcr:mixinTypes="[mix:versionable]"
        jcr:primaryType="cq:PageContent"
        jcr:title="Worldline files its document de base with the French Autorité des marchés financiers (AMF)"
        jcr:uuid="4c07a8fb-a7b4-4cef-8853-a533a435e01a"
        sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/pages/releasearticle"
        brand="worldline"
        categories_x0040_TypeHint="String[]"
        creationDate="{Date}2014-05-07T10:00:00.000+02:00"
        hideInNav="false"
        imagePath="/content/dam/gotomarket/uploads/bg-header-industries.jpg"
        keywords="worldline, amf"
        showbrand="false"
        showinfostrip="false">
        <head
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/head"/>
        <headlibs
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/headlibs"/>
        <header
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/header">
            <leftnavigation
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/leftnavigation"
                iconClass="iconClass2"/>
            <rightnavigation
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/rightnavigation"
                iconClass="iconClass2">
                <countrylistdropdown
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/countrylistdropdown"/>
                <languagedropdown
                    jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                    sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/languagedropdown"/>
            </rightnavigation>
            <mainnav
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/mainnav"/>
            <infostrip
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/infostrip"/>
            <breadcrumb
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/breadcrumb"/>
        </header>
        <headerpage
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/headerpage"/>
        <releasetitle
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/releasetitle"/>
        <key
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/parsys">
            <releasekeymessages
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/releasekeymessages"/>
        </key>
        <releasedescription
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/releasedescription"/>
        <prshare
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/prshare"/>
        <footer
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/footer">
            <sitemap
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/sitemap"/>
            <followus
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/followus"/>
            <newsletterform
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/newsletterform"/>
        </footer>
        <footlibs
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/footlibs"/>
        <copyright
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/structure/copyright"/>
        <content
            jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
            sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/parsys">
            <grid
                jcr:created="{Date}2017-08-29T16:57:17.665+02:00"
                jcr:createdBy="a101309"
                jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-08-29T16:57:17.665+02:00"
                jcr:lastModifiedBy="a101309"
                jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/layout/grid">
                <column1 jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured">
                    <richtext
                        jcr:created="{Date}2017-08-29T16:57:27.965+02:00"
                        jcr:createdBy="a101309"
                        jcr:lastModified="{Date}2017-08-29T17:05:23.270+02:00"
                        jcr:lastModifiedBy="a101309"
                        jcr:primaryType="nt:unstructured"
                        sling:resourceType="gotomarket/components/content/richtext"
                        text="&lt;p>&lt;i>This press release may not be distributed, directly or indirectly, in the United States, Canada, Australia or Japan&lt;/i>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>7 may 2014 - Worldline announces today the registration of its document de base with the French Autorité des marchés financiers (AMF) on 6 May 2014 under number I.14 - 027.&lt;/b>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>Registration of the document de base is the first step towards the initial public offering of its shares on the regulated market of Euronext in Paris. The process is subject to the AMF's granting of its visa on the prospectus for the transaction.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;blockquote>&lt;span class=&quot;block--featured--title&quot;>Gilles Grapinet, CEO of Worldline, said: &lt;/span>&amp;quot; I am very pleased to announce today this important step towards the forthcoming IPO of World l ine. With this IPO, Worldline will significantly increase its strategic and financial flexibility to seize opportunities and enlarge its footprint in the fast moving and rapidly growing payment markets. We are confident that with the continued support of Atos, Worldline will reinforce its European leadership in payment services and thanks to its highly skilled teams, will successfully deliver its strategic goals. &amp;quot;&lt;/blockquote>&#xa;&lt;p>Worldline' s document de base is available on the websites of the company (worldline.com) and of the AMF (www.amf-france.org), and free of charge and upon request to the company at 80 quai Voltaire, Immeuble River Ouest, 95870 Bezons, France. The compan y draws the public's attention to Chapter 4 &amp;quot;Risk Factors&amp;quot; of the document de base registered with the AMF.&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h3>Contacts&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Investor Relations:&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xa;Gilles Arditti&lt;br>&#xa;Tel +33 (0) 1 73 26 00 66&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;a title=&quot;gilles.arditti@atos.net&quot; href=&quot;mailto:gilles.arditti@atos.net&quot;>gilles.arditti@atos.net&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;b>Press:&lt;/b>&lt;br>&#xa;Caroline Crouch&lt;br>&#xa;Tel +44 77 33 310086&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;a title=&quot;caroline.crouch@atos.net&quot; href=&quot;mailto:caroline.crouch@atos.net&quot;>caroline.crouch@atos.net&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>David Sturken&lt;br>&#xa;Tel +44 20 7379 5151&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;a title=&quot;dsturken@maitland.co.uk&quot; href=&quot;mailto:dsturken@maitland.co.uk&quot;>dsturken@maitland.co.uk&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h3>About Worldline:&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>Worldline, an Atos subsidiary, is a major player in the European payments and transactional services industry, with an expanding emerging markets footprint. Worldline delivers new - generation services, enabling its customers to offer smooth and innovative s olutions to the end consumer. Key actor for B2B2C industries, with 40 years of experience, Worldline is ideally positioned to support and contribute to the success of businesses and administrative services in a perpetually evolving market. Worldline offers a unique and flexible business model built around a global and growing portfolio, thus enabling end - to - end support. Worldline's activities are organized around three axes: Merchant Services and Terminals, Mobility and e - Transactional Services, Financial P rocessing Services and Software Licensing. In 2013, Worldline's activities within the Atos Group generated (pro forma) revenues of 1.12 billion euros. The company employs m ore than 7,200 people worldwide .&lt;br>&#xa;&lt;a title=&quot;worldline. com&quot; href=&quot;http://www.worldline. com&quot;>worldline. com&lt;i>&lt;/i>&lt;/a>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;h3>Disclaimer&lt;/h3>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;i>No communication or other information related to this transaction or to Worldline may be transmitted to the public in a country in which any approval or registration is required. No steps to such end have been taken (or will be taken) by the company in any country (other than France) in which such steps would be required.&lt;/i>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;i>This press release does not constitute a prospectus within the meaning of Directive 2003/71/CE of the European Parliament and Council dated November 4, 2003, as amended, in particular by Directive 2010/73/UE to the extent implemented in the member states of the European Economic Area (together, the &amp;quot;Prospectus Directive&amp;quot;).&lt;/i>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;i>The offer will be open to the public in France after the delivery by the AMF of a visa on a Prospectu s composed of the document de base and a note d'opération that will be subsequently submitted to the AMF.&lt;/i>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;i>With respect to the member states of the European Economic Area other than France (the &amp;quot;Member States&amp;quot;) having implemented the Prospectus Directive i nto law, no action has been or will be taken in order to permit a public offer of the securities which would require the publication of a prospectus in one of such member states. In any EEA Member State other than France that has implemented the Prospectus Directive, this communication is only addressed to and is only directed at qualified investors in that Member State within the meaning of the Prospectus Directive.&lt;/i>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;i>These materials are not an offer for sale of Worldline shares in the United States or in any other jurisdiction. Worldline shares may not be sold in the United States absent registration or an exemption from registration under the U.S. Securities Act of 1933, as amended. Worldline does not intend to register any portion of the offering in the United States or to conduct a public offering of the shares in the United States. Any shares sold in the United States will be sold only to qualified institutional buyers (as defined in Rule 144A under the U.S. Securities Act of 1933, as amended) pursuant to Rule 144A.&lt;/i>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;i>This document is only being distributed to and is only directed at (i) persons who are outside the United Kingdom or (ii) to investment professionals falling within Article 19(5) of the Financial Services and Markets Act 2000 (Financial Promo tion) Order 2005 (the &amp;quot;Order&amp;quot;) or (iii) high net worth companies, and other persons to whom it may lawfully be communicated, falling within Article 49(2)(a) to (d) of the Order (all such persons in (i), (ii) and (iii) above together being referred to as &amp;quot;r elevant persons&amp;quot;). The Shares are only available to, and any invitation, offer or agreement to subscribe, purchase or otherwise acquire such securities will be engaged in only with, relevant persons. Any person who is not a relevant person should not act o r rely on this document or any of its contents.&lt;/i>&lt;/p>&#xa;&lt;p>&lt;i>Circulation of this press release in certain countries may result in a violation of applicable law. This press release should not be published, circulated or distributed, directly or indirectly, within the Un ited States, Canada, Australia or Japan.&lt;/i>&lt;/p>&#xa;"
                        textIsRich="true"/>
                </column1>
            </grid>
        </content>
    </jcr:content>
</jcr:root>
